[
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000114",
        "customerName": "Alonso Faulkner",
        "phoneNumber": "7369370108",
        "email": "alonso.faulkner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#16",
            "addressLine1": "The Village View",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 551247
        },
        "quantity": 978,
        "orderedDate": "2025-02-22T00:05:45.519Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-02-25T00:05:45.519Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alonso",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#16, The Village View, Bittan Market, Motihari, Bihar. 551247"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000179",
        "customerName": "Hadassah Curtis",
        "phoneNumber": "9980771227",
        "email": "hadassah.curtis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Park Central Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 562787
        },
        "quantity": 595,
        "orderedDate": "2025-02-19T10:21:18.676Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-02-22T10:21:18.676Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hadassah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 74,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Park Central Apartments, Berasia Road, Madgaon, Goa. 562787"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000258",
        "customerName": "Griffin Thomas",
        "phoneNumber": "7252790499",
        "email": "griffin.thomas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#36",
            "addressLine1": "Useful Units",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 432304
        },
        "quantity": 196,
        "orderedDate": "2025-02-06T12:35:38.445Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-02-09T12:35:38.445Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Griffin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#36, Useful Units, MP Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 432304"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000328",
        "customerName": "Cillian Stewart",
        "phoneNumber": "6199033885",
        "email": "cillian.stewart@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "The Village View",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 629308
        },
        "quantity": 434,
        "orderedDate": "2025-02-06T08:44:15.650Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-02-09T08:44:15.650Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cillian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, The Village View, Shivaji Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 629308"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000015",
        "customerName": "Mariam Carroll",
        "phoneNumber": "8506489100",
        "email": "mariam.carroll@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#16",
            "addressLine1": "The Niche Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 217028
        },
        "quantity": 888,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-30T18:43:25.742Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-02-02T18:43:25.742Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mariam",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 58,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#16, The Niche Apartments, Marvadi Road, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 217028"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000240",
        "customerName": "Arjun Scott",
        "phoneNumber": "8609958588",
        "email": "arjun.scott@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#76",
            "addressLine1": "Lilli Midtown Flats",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 685161
        },
        "quantity": 970,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-24T04:10:28.412Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-27T04:10:28.412Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Arjun",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#76, Lilli Midtown Flats, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 685161"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000302",
        "customerName": "Enzo Chandler",
        "phoneNumber": "8723599618",
        "email": "enzo.chandler@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "Broadway Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 460558
        },
        "quantity": 986,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-15T17:14:23.471Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-18T17:14:23.471Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Enzo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 39,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, Broadway Lofts, MP Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 460558"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000212",
        "customerName": "Zayne Quinn",
        "phoneNumber": "9575635260",
        "email": "zayne.quinn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#13",
            "addressLine1": "GreenHexa Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 783946
        },
        "quantity": 377,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-11T22:16:02.482Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-14T22:16:02.482Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zayne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#13, GreenHexa Realty Rental, Malviya Nagar, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 783946"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000216",
        "customerName": "Israel Savage",
        "phoneNumber": "9798734820",
        "email": "israel.savage@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Seaview Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 303747
        },
        "quantity": 768,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-10T13:44:59.836Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-13T13:44:59.836Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Israel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 86,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Seaview Apartments, Raisen Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 303747"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000099",
        "customerName": "Kai Mejia",
        "phoneNumber": "7394428712",
        "email": "kai.mejia@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#84",
            "addressLine1": "Grand at the Dominion",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Palanpur",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 229540
        },
        "quantity": 813,
        "orderedDate": "2025-01-05T00:23:17.576Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-08T00:23:17.576Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kai",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#84, Grand at the Dominion, Jawahar Chowk, Palanpur, Gujarat. 229540"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000495",
        "customerName": "Artemis Bonilla",
        "phoneNumber": "6682606649",
        "email": "artemis.bonilla@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Creekside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 109361
        },
        "quantity": 165,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-30T00:33:56.279Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2025-01-02T00:33:56.279Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Artemis",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Creekside Apartments, Jawahar Chowk, Guwahati, Assam. 109361"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000016",
        "customerName": "Oscar Callahan",
        "phoneNumber": "8065019647",
        "email": "oscar.callahan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#95",
            "addressLine1": "MasterGlory",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Amreli",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 263711
        },
        "quantity": 922,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-27T01:56:33.514Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-12-30T01:56:33.514Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Oscar",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#95, MasterGlory, MP Nagar, Amreli, Gujarat. 263711"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000336",
        "customerName": "Augustine Campbell",
        "phoneNumber": "7085771094",
        "email": "augustine.campbell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "The Niche Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 605425
        },
        "quantity": 147,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-12T06:08:17.993Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-12-15T06:08:17.993Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Augustine",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, The Niche Apartments, Habib Ganj, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 605425"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000237",
        "customerName": "Tori Roth",
        "phoneNumber": "7525011814",
        "email": "tori.roth@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "The Fedora",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Samastipur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 600960
        },
        "quantity": 701,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-12T03:20:55.792Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-12-15T03:20:55.792Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tori",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, The Fedora, Peer Gate, Samastipur, Bihar. 600960"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000069",
        "customerName": "Mckinley Hickman",
        "phoneNumber": "9947628346",
        "email": "mckinley.hickman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 481132
        },
        "quantity": 933,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-10T20:50:54.909Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-12-13T20:50:54.909Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mckinley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, City Dwellers, Berasia Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 481132"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000247",
        "customerName": "Leona Tucker",
        "phoneNumber": "8206689905",
        "email": "leona.tucker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Homes with peace",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Palanpur",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 735207
        },
        "quantity": 931,
        "orderedDate": "2024-12-10T05:14:43.906Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-12-13T05:14:43.906Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leona",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Homes with peace, Govind Pura, Palanpur, Gujarat. 735207"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000437",
        "customerName": "Allyson Robinson",
        "phoneNumber": "6652266064",
        "email": "allyson.robinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "The Dorm Room",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 440125
        },
        "quantity": 568,
        "orderedDate": "2024-11-16T20:42:47.541Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-11-19T20:42:47.541Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Allyson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 17,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, The Dorm Room, Shahpura, Dispur, Assam. 440125"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000272",
        "customerName": "Lionel Horton",
        "phoneNumber": "8553890110",
        "email": "lionel.horton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Homes for all",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Dibrugarh",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 779210
        },
        "quantity": 278,
        "orderedDate": "2024-11-16T17:15:26.250Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-11-19T17:15:26.250Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lionel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 54,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Homes for all, Hoshangabad Road, Dibrugarh, Assam. 779210"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000409",
        "customerName": "Zariah Frank",
        "phoneNumber": "7823688244",
        "email": "zariah.frank@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#82",
            "addressLine1": "Broadway Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 627482
        },
        "quantity": 925,
        "orderedDate": "2024-11-06T10:30:05.138Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-11-09T10:30:05.138Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zariah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#82, Broadway Lofts, Kolar Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 627482"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000194",
        "customerName": "Bruno Tate",
        "phoneNumber": "7511638216",
        "email": "bruno.tate@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "ApHEARTments",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Saharsa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 654648
        },
        "quantity": 632,
        "orderedDate": "2024-11-04T14:37:15.725Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-11-07T14:37:15.725Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Bruno",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, ApHEARTments, Raisen Road, Saharsa, Bihar. 654648"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000479",
        "customerName": "Remi McPherson",
        "phoneNumber": "9011267324",
        "email": "remi.mcpherson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#86",
            "addressLine1": "Nature Custom",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Begusarai",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 218126
        },
        "quantity": 509,
        "orderedDate": "2024-10-25T04:24:12.277Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-28T04:24:12.277Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Remi",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#86, Nature Custom, Peer Gate, Begusarai, Bihar. 218126"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000477",
        "customerName": "Melissa Montoya",
        "phoneNumber": "6581943773",
        "email": "melissa.montoya@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "The City Block",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 178091
        },
        "quantity": 314,
        "orderedDate": "2024-10-22T07:20:58.048Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-25T07:20:58.048Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Melissa",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 40,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, The City Block, Marvadi Road, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 178091"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000215",
        "customerName": "Dahlia Rios",
        "phoneNumber": "7700322280",
        "email": "dahlia.rios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Peace apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Palanpur",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 192553
        },
        "quantity": 779,
        "orderedDate": "2024-10-18T01:19:46.365Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-21T01:19:46.365Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dahlia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Peace apartments, Peer Gate, Palanpur, Gujarat. 192553"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000332",
        "customerName": "Moshe Bowman",
        "phoneNumber": "8542835868",
        "email": "moshe.bowman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#92",
            "addressLine1": "Village Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Bhagalpur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 441648
        },
        "quantity": 771,
        "orderedDate": "2024-10-13T10:20:48.668Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-16T10:20:48.668Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Moshe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#92, Village Homes, Bairagarh, Bhagalpur, Bihar. 441648"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000334",
        "customerName": "Hassan Boyer",
        "phoneNumber": "8839756732",
        "email": "hassan.boyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "EcoStay",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 217007
        },
        "quantity": 725,
        "orderedDate": "2024-10-07T04:23:53.503Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-10T04:23:53.503Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hassan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 39,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, EcoStay, Bittan Market, Silchar, Assam. 217007"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000011",
        "customerName": "Yara Baxter",
        "phoneNumber": "6144918303",
        "email": "yara.baxter@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Village Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 354902
        },
        "quantity": 801,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-30T21:16:46.371Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-03T21:16:46.371Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Yara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Village Homes, Jawahar Chowk, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 354902"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000299",
        "customerName": "Hadley Bowen",
        "phoneNumber": "7114590834",
        "email": "hadley.bowen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "The Mill",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Adoni",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 534744
        },
        "quantity": 593,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-30T15:15:23.476Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-03T15:15:23.476Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hadley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, The Mill, Kolar Road, Adoni, Andhra Pradesh. 534744"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000269",
        "customerName": "Paola Shaw",
        "phoneNumber": "7475972734",
        "email": "paola.shaw@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "CappaCale Dale",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 868075
        },
        "quantity": 296,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-29T20:29:14.434Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-02T20:29:14.434Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paola",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 47,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, CappaCale Dale, Govind Pura, Dispur, Assam. 868075"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000415",
        "customerName": "Aarya Leblanc",
        "phoneNumber": "7923132470",
        "email": "aarya.leblanc@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#97",
            "addressLine1": "RealBond Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 276283
        },
        "quantity": 583,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-28T06:45:56.829Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-10-01T06:45:56.829Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aarya",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#97, RealBond Realty Rental, Shahpura, New Delhi, Delhi. 276283"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000359",
        "customerName": "Kyla Hodge",
        "phoneNumber": "6876700941",
        "email": "kyla.hodge@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "Newport Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Surendranagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 682756
        },
        "quantity": 860,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-21T23:06:33.422Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-09-24T23:06:33.422Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kyla",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 78,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, Newport Apartments, Hamidia Road, Surendranagar, Gujarat. 682756"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000236",
        "customerName": "Dominic Reilly",
        "phoneNumber": "7026854968",
        "email": "dominic.reilly@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Skyline Condo",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 821760
        },
        "quantity": 630,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-09T17:23:25.375Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-09-12T17:23:25.375Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dominic",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Skyline Condo, MP Nagar, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 821760"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000223",
        "customerName": "Salem Jacobs",
        "phoneNumber": "7546698767",
        "email": "salem.jacobs@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "The Dorm Room",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 851176
        },
        "quantity": 217,
        "orderedDate": "2024-09-06T00:27:41.131Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-09-09T00:27:41.131Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Salem",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, The Dorm Room, Berasia Road, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 851176"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000392",
        "customerName": "Rex Graves",
        "phoneNumber": "7123558365",
        "email": "rex.graves@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#59",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 733620
        },
        "quantity": 314,
        "orderedDate": "2024-08-29T13:50:35.608Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-09-01T13:50:35.608Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rex",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#59, The Bend, Raisen Road, Silchar, Assam. 733620"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000469",
        "customerName": "Cali Rubio",
        "phoneNumber": "7746124873",
        "email": "cali.rubio@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Sun’s Rays Place",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 521622
        },
        "quantity": 659,
        "orderedDate": "2024-08-25T22:41:52.405Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-28T22:41:52.405Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cali",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 17,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Sun’s Rays Place, Hamidia Road, Guwahati, Assam. 521622"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000105",
        "customerName": "Denisse Lloyd",
        "phoneNumber": "8899345034",
        "email": "denisse.lloyd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#43",
            "addressLine1": "GreenHexa Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Guntur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 525024
        },
        "quantity": 113,
        "orderedDate": "2024-08-17T04:21:31.437Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-20T04:21:31.437Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Denisse",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 90,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#43, GreenHexa Realty Rental, Peer Gate, Guntur, Andhra Pradesh. 525024"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000049",
        "customerName": "Ashlynn Rios",
        "phoneNumber": "8286800505",
        "email": "ashlynn.rios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "The City Block",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 984807
        },
        "quantity": 225,
        "orderedDate": "2024-08-14T22:46:05.299Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-17T22:46:05.299Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ashlynn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 33,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, The City Block, Govind Pura, Panaji, Goa. 984807"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000078",
        "customerName": "Jaxton Horton",
        "phoneNumber": "9401581533",
        "email": "jaxton.horton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#85",
            "addressLine1": "WinterSpring Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 328991
        },
        "quantity": 493,
        "orderedDate": "2024-08-09T15:52:07.557Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-12T15:52:07.557Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jaxton",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#85, WinterSpring Rental, Koh E Fiza, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 328991"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000431",
        "customerName": "Sariah Blankenship",
        "phoneNumber": "9952115976",
        "email": "sariah.blankenship@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#76",
            "addressLine1": "Apartment Partners",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 292667
        },
        "quantity": 280,
        "orderedDate": "2024-07-31T00:20:32.323Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-03T00:20:32.323Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sariah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#76, Apartment Partners, Kolar Road, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 292667"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000023",
        "customerName": "Corinne Hensley",
        "phoneNumber": "9797587540",
        "email": "corinne.hensley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "The Fedora",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 818454
        },
        "quantity": 375,
        "orderedDate": "2024-07-30T05:12:56.317Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-08-02T05:12:56.317Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Corinne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, The Fedora, Arera Colony, Motihari, Bihar. 818454"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000063",
        "customerName": "Fallon Little",
        "phoneNumber": "6149134094",
        "email": "fallon.little@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#49",
            "addressLine1": "Soft bed rentals",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 264741
        },
        "quantity": 391,
        "orderedDate": "2024-07-22T12:05:16.791Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-07-25T12:05:16.791Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Fallon",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#49, Soft bed rentals, Shahpura, Madgaon, Goa. 264741"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000156",
        "customerName": "Arturo Carson",
        "phoneNumber": "7241565238",
        "email": "arturo.carson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#27",
            "addressLine1": "The City Block",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 308073
        },
        "quantity": 474,
        "orderedDate": "2024-07-08T03:38:07.541Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-07-11T03:38:07.541Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Arturo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#27, The City Block, Bairagarh, Delhi, Delhi. 308073"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000491",
        "customerName": "Mabel Gilmore",
        "phoneNumber": "9177214824",
        "email": "mabel.gilmore@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "Soft bed rentals",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Samastipur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 687786
        },
        "quantity": 400,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-23T08:50:21.218Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-26T08:50:21.218Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mabel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, Soft bed rentals, Hamidia Road, Samastipur, Bihar. 687786"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000161",
        "customerName": "Carly Schmitt",
        "phoneNumber": "7779811171",
        "email": "carly.schmitt@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#12",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Saharsa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 101044
        },
        "quantity": 361,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-18T07:39:12.055Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-21T07:39:12.055Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Carly",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 22,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#12, Sunshine Apartments, Hamidia Road, Saharsa, Bihar. 101044"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000429",
        "customerName": "Monica Burton",
        "phoneNumber": "8572246580",
        "email": "monica.burton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "Peace apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Jamnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 721748
        },
        "quantity": 973,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-14T14:54:08.558Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-17T14:54:08.558Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Monica",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, Peace apartments, Jawahar Chowk, Jamnagar, Gujarat. 721748"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000443",
        "customerName": "Lea Strong",
        "phoneNumber": "8074789590",
        "email": "lea.strong@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "The Niche Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 192781
        },
        "quantity": 381,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-10T13:04:38.305Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-13T13:04:38.305Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lea",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, The Niche Apartments, Berasia Road, Tezpur, Assam. 192781"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000344",
        "customerName": "Kamden Hendricks",
        "phoneNumber": "6465208775",
        "email": "kamden.hendricks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#76",
            "addressLine1": "The Fedora",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 727437
        },
        "quantity": 590,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-09T12:15:38.324Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-12T12:15:38.324Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kamden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#76, The Fedora, Malviya Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 727437"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000389",
        "customerName": "Alani McBride",
        "phoneNumber": "6495387668",
        "email": "alani.mcbride@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Canyon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 233166
        },
        "quantity": 520,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-07T04:20:40.664Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-10T04:20:40.664Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 74,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Hillside Canyon Apartments, Marvadi Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 233166"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000028",
        "customerName": "Jaden Rasmussen",
        "phoneNumber": "8632909914",
        "email": "jaden.rasmussen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Carriage House",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 258856
        },
        "quantity": 533,
        "orderedDate": "2024-06-02T13:54:59.216Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-05T13:54:59.216Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jaden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 61,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Carriage House, Habib Ganj, New Delhi, Delhi. 258856"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000455",
        "customerName": "Priscilla Pope",
        "phoneNumber": "7526753540",
        "email": "priscilla.pope@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Ample Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 910703
        },
        "quantity": 125,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-30T00:19:56.443Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-06-02T00:19:56.443Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Priscilla",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Ample Apartments, Marvadi Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 910703"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000250",
        "customerName": "Clay Garrett",
        "phoneNumber": "6180796056",
        "email": "clay.garrett@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#97",
            "addressLine1": "Merril Willow Rental Co.",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Kadapa",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 166422
        },
        "quantity": 961,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-21T20:27:59.993Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-24T20:27:59.993Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Clay",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#97, Merril Willow Rental Co., Hoshangabad Road, Kadapa, Andhra Pradesh. 166422"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000154",
        "customerName": "Jacob Conner",
        "phoneNumber": "9293500142",
        "email": "jacob.conner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Village Villas",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 599164
        },
        "quantity": 875,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-21T04:32:13.685Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-24T04:32:13.685Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jacob",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 90,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Village Villas, TT Nagar, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 599164"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000283",
        "customerName": "Astrid Brooks",
        "phoneNumber": "8884652045",
        "email": "astrid.brooks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 237141
        },
        "quantity": 130,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-08T18:14:52.463Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-11T18:14:52.463Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Astrid",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 44,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, City Dwellers, Shahpura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 237141"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000222",
        "customerName": "Jay Conley",
        "phoneNumber": "7825637010",
        "email": "jay.conley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#43",
            "addressLine1": "Four Flamingo",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Veraval",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 622186
        },
        "quantity": 905,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-06T07:56:45.108Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-09T07:56:45.108Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jay",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#43, Four Flamingo, Bairagarh, Veraval, Gujarat. 622186"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000115",
        "customerName": "Ansley Kerr",
        "phoneNumber": "8261453155",
        "email": "ansley.kerr@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#68",
            "addressLine1": "Four Flamingo",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 486994
        },
        "quantity": 326,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-04T13:30:19.902Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-07T13:30:19.902Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ansley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#68, Four Flamingo, Govind Pura, Madgaon, Goa. 486994"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000188",
        "customerName": "Marlon Anthony",
        "phoneNumber": "8941295563",
        "email": "marlon.anthony@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Harmony Park",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 278477
        },
        "quantity": 462,
        "orderedDate": "2024-05-04T06:34:35.967Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-07T06:34:35.967Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marlon",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Harmony Park, Koh E Fiza, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 278477"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000045",
        "customerName": "Paislee Wilkins",
        "phoneNumber": "6571030536",
        "email": "paislee.wilkins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Chapra",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 127147
        },
        "quantity": 833,
        "orderedDate": "2024-04-30T19:51:18.333Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-03T19:51:18.333Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paislee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 40,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Jolly City, Arera Colony, Chapra, Bihar. 127147"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000253",
        "customerName": "Eden Levy",
        "phoneNumber": "6397630719",
        "email": "eden.levy@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#43",
            "addressLine1": "Concrete homes",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 177241
        },
        "quantity": 277,
        "orderedDate": "2024-04-29T10:59:49.282Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-05-02T10:59:49.282Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#43, Concrete homes, Jawahar Chowk, Panaji, Goa. 177241"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000355",
        "customerName": "Whitley Lloyd",
        "phoneNumber": "8761214295",
        "email": "whitley.lloyd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Timber Ridge Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Vizianagaram",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 721086
        },
        "quantity": 539,
        "orderedDate": "2024-04-27T17:07:41.412Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-04-30T17:07:41.412Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Whitley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Timber Ridge Apartments, Berasia Road, Vizianagaram, Andhra Pradesh. 721086"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000436",
        "customerName": "Kyler Vincent",
        "phoneNumber": "8286042208",
        "email": "kyler.vincent@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#75",
            "addressLine1": "Four Flamingo",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 669162
        },
        "quantity": 820,
        "orderedDate": "2024-04-25T02:32:58.309Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-04-28T02:32:58.309Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kyler",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 79,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#75, Four Flamingo, Raisen Road, Panaji, Goa. 669162"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000391",
        "customerName": "Kelly Hancock",
        "phoneNumber": "6369453375",
        "email": "kelly.hancock@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Blue Ribbon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Katihar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 715396
        },
        "quantity": 212,
        "orderedDate": "2024-04-08T23:15:25.802Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-04-11T23:15:25.802Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kelly",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 45,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Blue Ribbon Apartments, Peer Gate, Katihar, Bihar. 715396"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000317",
        "customerName": "Nataly Moore",
        "phoneNumber": "7362717050",
        "email": "nataly.moore@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#29",
            "addressLine1": "Stanley Park Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Rajkot",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 377511
        },
        "quantity": 822,
        "orderedDate": "2024-03-12T02:37:39.185Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-03-15T02:37:39.185Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nataly",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#29, Stanley Park Apartments, Indrapuri, Rajkot, Gujarat. 377511"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000472",
        "customerName": "Enzo Hopkins",
        "phoneNumber": "6680758155",
        "email": "enzo.hopkins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "Useful Units",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 759083
        },
        "quantity": 990,
        "orderedDate": "2024-03-11T05:33:16.927Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-03-14T05:33:16.927Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Enzo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 96,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, Useful Units, Jahangirabad, Madgaon, Goa. 759083"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000066",
        "customerName": "Reece Mendez",
        "phoneNumber": "9576939516",
        "email": "reece.mendez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "The River",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Raipur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 774516
        },
        "quantity": 789,
        "orderedDate": "2024-03-10T17:22:28.262Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-03-13T17:22:28.262Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Reece",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, The River, TT Nagar, Raipur, Chhattisgarh. 774516"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000480",
        "customerName": "Foster Skinner",
        "phoneNumber": "6743792045",
        "email": "foster.skinner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Place",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Vijayawada",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 150989
        },
        "quantity": 129,
        "orderedDate": "2024-03-10T01:18:16.869Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-03-13T01:18:16.869Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Foster",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 45,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, Sunshine Place, Raisen Road, Vijayawada, Andhra Pradesh. 150989"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000457",
        "customerName": "Legacy Dennis",
        "phoneNumber": "9710425043",
        "email": "legacy.dennis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 642019
        },
        "quantity": 853,
        "orderedDate": "2024-03-06T11:37:54.695Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-03-09T11:37:54.695Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Legacy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, La Grande Maison, Peer Gate, Tinsukia, Assam. 642019"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000281",
        "customerName": "Malia McMahon",
        "phoneNumber": "7300874742",
        "email": "malia.mcmahon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#24",
            "addressLine1": "Creekside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Chittoor",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 775645
        },
        "quantity": 105,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-22T21:11:33.609Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-25T21:11:33.609Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Malia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#24, Creekside Apartments, Peer Gate, Chittoor, Andhra Pradesh. 775645"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000139",
        "customerName": "Leilany Ingram",
        "phoneNumber": "6708277967",
        "email": "leilany.ingram@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "Park Place",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 314215
        },
        "quantity": 899,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-21T16:17:51.410Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-24T16:17:51.410Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leilany",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 48,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, Park Place, Hamidia Road, Madgaon, Goa. 314215"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000195",
        "customerName": "Skye Robinson",
        "phoneNumber": "9330788229",
        "email": "skye.robinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#29",
            "addressLine1": "Broadway Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 895773
        },
        "quantity": 356,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-21T05:43:35.655Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-24T05:43:35.655Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Skye",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#29, Broadway Lofts, Shahpura, Panaji, Goa. 895773"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000185",
        "customerName": "Eliza Jones",
        "phoneNumber": "8770099510",
        "email": "eliza.jones@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "WinterSpring Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Vizianagaram",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 752609
        },
        "quantity": 190,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-12T14:51:14.021Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-15T14:51:14.021Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eliza",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, WinterSpring Rental, Indrapuri, Vizianagaram, Andhra Pradesh. 752609"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000197",
        "customerName": "Maci Henderson",
        "phoneNumber": "8438625679",
        "email": "maci.henderson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#61",
            "addressLine1": "Youth Motive",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Ahmadabad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 976012
        },
        "quantity": 914,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-12T00:27:51.327Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-15T00:27:51.327Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maci",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#61, Youth Motive, Sultania Road, Ahmadabad, Gujarat. 976012"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000277",
        "customerName": "Adriana Dickerson",
        "phoneNumber": "6228339292",
        "email": "adriana.dickerson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "Soft bed rentals",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 662891
        },
        "quantity": 382,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-09T05:16:09.227Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-12T05:16:09.227Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Adriana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 24,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, Soft bed rentals, Kolar Road, Delhi, Delhi. 662891"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000349",
        "customerName": "Collins Davis",
        "phoneNumber": "9819940392",
        "email": "collins.davis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#21",
            "addressLine1": "Carriage House",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 271363
        },
        "quantity": 438,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-08T06:00:02.341Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-11T06:00:02.341Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Collins",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#21, Carriage House, Shahpura, New Delhi, Delhi. 271363"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000172",
        "customerName": "Maximilian Kemp",
        "phoneNumber": "8306968553",
        "email": "maximilian.kemp@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#26",
            "addressLine1": "Etta Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 753895
        },
        "quantity": 678,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-08T00:51:08.571Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-11T00:51:08.571Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maximilian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#26, Etta Apartments, Raisen Road, Panaji, Goa. 753895"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000388",
        "customerName": "Allen Delgado",
        "phoneNumber": "7902908567",
        "email": "allen.delgado@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Creekside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Valsad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 385087
        },
        "quantity": 662,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-07T02:17:41.470Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-10T02:17:41.470Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Allen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 48,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Creekside Apartments, Malviya Nagar, Valsad, Gujarat. 385087"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000057",
        "customerName": "Marie McMillan",
        "phoneNumber": "6913218158",
        "email": "marie.mcmillan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "The Jacks",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Jorhat",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 499412
        },
        "quantity": 810,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-06T08:51:13.979Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-09T08:51:13.979Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 85,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, The Jacks, Kolar Road, Jorhat, Assam. 499412"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000221",
        "customerName": "Ava Fletcher",
        "phoneNumber": "9575633725",
        "email": "ava.fletcher@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "The Village View",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 216683
        },
        "quantity": 454,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-04T15:21:58.028Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-07T15:21:58.028Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ava",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, The Village View, Arera Colony, Dispur, Assam. 216683"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000019",
        "customerName": "Adeline Schwartz",
        "phoneNumber": "9812757038",
        "email": "adeline.schwartz@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Peace Waters",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 938531
        },
        "quantity": 977,
        "orderedDate": "2024-02-03T12:02:44.046Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-06T12:02:44.046Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Adeline",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Peace Waters, Shahpura, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 938531"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000452",
        "customerName": "Landyn Shepherd",
        "phoneNumber": "7651465030",
        "email": "landyn.shepherd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "The Palm Springs",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Bhavnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 610311
        },
        "quantity": 420,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-31T17:44:09.471Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-02-03T17:44:09.471Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Landyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 43,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, The Palm Springs, Koh E Fiza, Bhavnagar, Gujarat. 610311"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000076",
        "customerName": "Saul Harris",
        "phoneNumber": "8598800615",
        "email": "saul.harris@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 752679
        },
        "quantity": 483,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-28T10:28:37.395Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-31T10:28:37.395Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Saul",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Hillside Apartments, Jahangirabad, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 752679"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000056",
        "customerName": "Moses Pittman",
        "phoneNumber": "6927383755",
        "email": "moses.pittman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Sunny Place",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 759368
        },
        "quantity": 872,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-27T06:22:57.704Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-30T06:22:57.704Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Moses",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Sunny Place, Koh E Fiza, Tezpur, Assam. 759368"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000298",
        "customerName": "Drake Gonzales",
        "phoneNumber": "7864475060",
        "email": "drake.gonzales@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#60",
            "addressLine1": "Standard At Legacy",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Surat",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 905804
        },
        "quantity": 691,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-26T22:10:56.338Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-29T22:10:56.338Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Drake",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 14,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#60, Standard At Legacy, Koh E Fiza, Surat, Gujarat. 905804"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000348",
        "customerName": "Shepard Benson",
        "phoneNumber": "9705499353",
        "email": "shepard.benson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Ample Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Purnia",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 253781
        },
        "quantity": 665,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-26T13:50:14.838Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-29T13:50:14.838Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Shepard",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Ample Apartments, Raisen Road, Purnia, Bihar. 253781"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000377",
        "customerName": "Rylie Cox",
        "phoneNumber": "8483854103",
        "email": "rylie.cox@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "Sunny Place",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Chandragiri",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 182485
        },
        "quantity": 871,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-23T16:08:01.218Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-26T16:08:01.218Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rylie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, Sunny Place, Berasia Road, Chandragiri, Andhra Pradesh. 182485"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000493",
        "customerName": "Arabella Arias",
        "phoneNumber": "7013269871",
        "email": "arabella.arias@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Etta Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Barauni",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 288192
        },
        "quantity": 274,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-20T18:07:02.266Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-23T18:07:02.266Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Arabella",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Etta Apartments, Indrapuri, Barauni, Bihar. 288192"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000061",
        "customerName": "Maliyah Wyatt",
        "phoneNumber": "9955135392",
        "email": "maliyah.wyatt@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "Eastern Suburbs",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Valsad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 799761
        },
        "quantity": 297,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-15T06:25:52.420Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-18T06:25:52.420Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maliyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 79,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, Eastern Suburbs, Peer Gate, Valsad, Gujarat. 799761"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000468",
        "customerName": "Jett Banks",
        "phoneNumber": "9766991090",
        "email": "jett.banks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#43",
            "addressLine1": "East Side Living",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Godhra",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 719369
        },
        "quantity": 228,
        "orderedDate": "2024-01-04T19:13:10.951Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2024-01-07T19:13:10.951Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jett",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#43, East Side Living, Habib Ganj, Godhra, Gujarat. 719369"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000160",
        "customerName": "Layne Monroe",
        "phoneNumber": "6259156961",
        "email": "layne.monroe@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Greenway Court Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Munger",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 836387
        },
        "quantity": 448,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-28T14:42:21.828Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-31T14:42:21.828Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Layne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 14,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Greenway Court Apartments, Habib Ganj, Munger, Bihar. 836387"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000381",
        "customerName": "Michelle Humphrey",
        "phoneNumber": "8948152092",
        "email": "michelle.humphrey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "Life on the Green",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 611319
        },
        "quantity": 383,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-21T17:06:00.232Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-24T17:06:00.232Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Michelle",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, Life on the Green, Hamidia Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 611319"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000101",
        "customerName": "Cora Harvey",
        "phoneNumber": "7286909358",
        "email": "cora.harvey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "Tropicana Del Norte",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Nagaon",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 679219
        },
        "quantity": 525,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-20T23:02:13.881Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-23T23:02:13.881Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cora",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, Tropicana Del Norte, Kolar Road, Nagaon, Assam. 679219"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000062",
        "customerName": "Sam Hahn",
        "phoneNumber": "9279739457",
        "email": "sam.hahn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Silver House",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 322313
        },
        "quantity": 528,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-12T09:58:23.251Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-15T09:58:23.251Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sam",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Silver House, Raisen Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 322313"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000109",
        "customerName": "Winnie Cisneros",
        "phoneNumber": "8072796368",
        "email": "winnie.cisneros@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "Seaview Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 551460
        },
        "quantity": 429,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-11T17:52:00.141Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-14T17:52:00.141Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Winnie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, Seaview Apartments, Sultania Road, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 551460"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000051",
        "customerName": "Madisyn Horn",
        "phoneNumber": "9251134070",
        "email": "madisyn.horn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#62",
            "addressLine1": "Nature Custom",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 511091
        },
        "quantity": 546,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-09T07:46:03.305Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-12T07:46:03.305Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Madisyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#62, Nature Custom, Hamidia Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 511091"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000126",
        "customerName": "Blaine Barker",
        "phoneNumber": "9864559303",
        "email": "blaine.barker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "Peace Waters",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 677390
        },
        "quantity": 188,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-07T20:38:20.485Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-10T20:38:20.485Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Blaine",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 22,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, Peace Waters, MP Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 677390"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000316",
        "customerName": "Camilo Booker",
        "phoneNumber": "9390483868",
        "email": "camilo.booker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "The Station",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 440131
        },
        "quantity": 500,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-03T18:52:06.421Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-06T18:52:06.421Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Camilo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 96,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, The Station, Hoshangabad Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 440131"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000462",
        "customerName": "Dariel Avery",
        "phoneNumber": "8909510172",
        "email": "dariel.avery@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "Timber Ridge Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 585418
        },
        "quantity": 845,
        "orderedDate": "2023-12-01T14:06:00.939Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-12-04T14:06:00.939Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dariel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, Timber Ridge Apartments, TT Nagar, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 585418"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000398",
        "customerName": "Nash Cantu",
        "phoneNumber": "7622432977",
        "email": "nash.cantu@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#68",
            "addressLine1": "Cove Property",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 937935
        },
        "quantity": 774,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-26T19:16:22.149Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-29T19:16:22.149Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nash",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#68, Cove Property, Bairagarh, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 937935"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000451",
        "customerName": "Alia Singleton",
        "phoneNumber": "7710840689",
        "email": "alia.singleton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "The Fedora",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Gandhinagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 871261
        },
        "quantity": 780,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-23T00:12:18.374Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-26T00:12:18.374Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 30,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, The Fedora, Jawahar Chowk, Gandhinagar, Gujarat. 871261"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000104",
        "customerName": "Maison Mays",
        "phoneNumber": "6828710971",
        "email": "maison.mays@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Spectrum on Spring",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 825587
        },
        "quantity": 698,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-21T02:52:59.195Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-24T02:52:59.195Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maison",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Spectrum on Spring, MP Nagar, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 825587"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000251",
        "customerName": "Tessa Cain",
        "phoneNumber": "6303593590",
        "email": "tessa.cain@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Passion homes",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 202600
        },
        "quantity": 770,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-10T00:43:14.008Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-13T00:43:14.008Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tessa",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 43,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Passion homes, Indrapuri, Madgaon, Goa. 202600"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000224",
        "customerName": "Bryan Jennings",
        "phoneNumber": "8607479086",
        "email": "bryan.jennings@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "Surf Rider Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 819843
        },
        "quantity": 397,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-05T03:09:15.720Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-08T03:09:15.720Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Bryan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, Surf Rider Apartments, Bittan Market, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 819843"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000142",
        "customerName": "Isaias Keller",
        "phoneNumber": "7756538717",
        "email": "isaias.keller@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Safe Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Mahesana",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 370376
        },
        "quantity": 408,
        "orderedDate": "2023-11-02T23:18:17.629Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-05T23:18:17.629Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Isaias",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Safe Homes, Jahangirabad, Mahesana, Gujarat. 370376"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000412",
        "customerName": "Jay Velasquez",
        "phoneNumber": "7694330010",
        "email": "jay.velasquez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Ideal homes",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 906995
        },
        "quantity": 342,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-31T02:32:56.384Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-03T02:32:56.384Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jay",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Ideal homes, MP Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 906995"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000373",
        "customerName": "Olivia Molina",
        "phoneNumber": "6296769279",
        "email": "olivia.molina@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Place",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 216379
        },
        "quantity": 523,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-30T13:58:53.976Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-11-02T13:58:53.976Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Olivia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 33,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Sunshine Place, Sultania Road, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 216379"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000196",
        "customerName": "Matthew Fischer",
        "phoneNumber": "6167380349",
        "email": "matthew.fischer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#16",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Machilipatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 682122
        },
        "quantity": 618,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-23T02:19:49.041Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-26T02:19:49.041Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Matthew",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#16, Jolly City, Shivaji Nagar, Machilipatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 682122"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000208",
        "customerName": "Stanley Hubbard",
        "phoneNumber": "8613595270",
        "email": "stanley.hubbard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Tropicana Del Norte",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Guntur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 827394
        },
        "quantity": 679,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-13T04:47:36.917Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-16T04:47:36.917Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Stanley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Tropicana Del Norte, Jahangirabad, Guntur, Andhra Pradesh. 827394"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000428",
        "customerName": "Taylor Marks",
        "phoneNumber": "9469145458",
        "email": "taylor.marks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "One Circular Quay",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 393778
        },
        "quantity": 637,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-12T01:11:49.198Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-15T01:11:49.198Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Taylor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 87,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, One Circular Quay, Jahangirabad, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 393778"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000264",
        "customerName": "Killian Porter",
        "phoneNumber": "9796051449",
        "email": "killian.porter@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "Ray White Residential",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 336682
        },
        "quantity": 616,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-11T20:03:39.813Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-14T20:03:39.813Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Killian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, Ray White Residential, TT Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 336682"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000326",
        "customerName": "Donovan Barnes",
        "phoneNumber": "8542444863",
        "email": "donovan.barnes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#21",
            "addressLine1": "MiniPalais",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Anantapur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 604081
        },
        "quantity": 278,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-11T04:37:24.670Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-14T04:37:24.670Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Donovan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#21, MiniPalais, Raisen Road, Anantapur, Andhra Pradesh. 604081"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000396",
        "customerName": "Amir Wiley",
        "phoneNumber": "8544963781",
        "email": "amir.wiley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#27",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Walkups",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Porbandar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 228948
        },
        "quantity": 768,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-06T14:25:19.101Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-09T14:25:19.101Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Amir",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#27, Town Place Walkups, TT Nagar, Porbandar, Gujarat. 228948"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000135",
        "customerName": "Jocelyn Collier",
        "phoneNumber": "7466323443",
        "email": "jocelyn.collier@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "Carriage House",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 289432
        },
        "quantity": 754,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-05T00:15:51.740Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-08T00:15:51.740Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jocelyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 52,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, Carriage House, Berasia Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 289432"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000204",
        "customerName": "Kye Haley",
        "phoneNumber": "8877081912",
        "email": "kye.haley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "Vertex condos",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Kakinada",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 356739
        },
        "quantity": 444,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-03T06:48:16.854Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-06T06:48:16.854Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kye",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, Vertex condos, Habib Ganj, Kakinada, Andhra Pradesh. 356739"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000228",
        "customerName": "Dario Ray",
        "phoneNumber": "8343455845",
        "email": "dario.ray@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#24",
            "addressLine1": "The Twin Towers",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 794764
        },
        "quantity": 589,
        "orderedDate": "2023-10-02T14:36:25.458Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-05T14:36:25.458Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dario",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#24, The Twin Towers, Hoshangabad Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 794764"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000481",
        "customerName": "Mara Salgado",
        "phoneNumber": "9310239359",
        "email": "mara.salgado@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Greenway Court Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 410428
        },
        "quantity": 904,
        "orderedDate": "2023-09-28T13:36:12.360Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-01T13:36:12.360Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 69,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Greenway Court Apartments, Shahpura, Tinsukia, Assam. 410428"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000182",
        "customerName": "Ronan Le",
        "phoneNumber": "9277657452",
        "email": "ronan.le@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Walkups",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Muzaffarpur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 618553
        },
        "quantity": 206,
        "orderedDate": "2023-09-28T08:39:20.713Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-10-01T08:39:20.713Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ronan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Town Place Walkups, Habib Ganj, Muzaffarpur, Bihar. 618553"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000367",
        "customerName": "Wren Good",
        "phoneNumber": "7841536051",
        "email": "wren.good@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "One Uptown",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Nagaon",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 320101
        },
        "quantity": 739,
        "orderedDate": "2023-09-06T17:45:36.441Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-09-09T17:45:36.441Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Wren",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, One Uptown, Marvadi Road, Nagaon, Assam. 320101"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000217",
        "customerName": "Louise Park",
        "phoneNumber": "6898507885",
        "email": "louise.park@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Apartment Partners",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 573688
        },
        "quantity": 679,
        "orderedDate": "2023-09-03T18:37:10.612Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-09-06T18:37:10.612Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Louise",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 86,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Apartment Partners, Shahpura, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 573688"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000129",
        "customerName": "Carter Decker",
        "phoneNumber": "6231255081",
        "email": "carter.decker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "Skyline Condo",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 357618
        },
        "quantity": 965,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-22T15:29:03.785Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-25T15:29:03.785Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Carter",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, Skyline Condo, Shahpura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 357618"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000157",
        "customerName": "Nalani Carroll",
        "phoneNumber": "6463068471",
        "email": "nalani.carroll@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#64",
            "addressLine1": "Ray White Residential",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 490991
        },
        "quantity": 975,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-15T09:57:06.875Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-18T09:57:06.875Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nalani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 85,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#64, Ray White Residential, Berasia Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 490991"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000288",
        "customerName": "Wyatt Felix",
        "phoneNumber": "6023447852",
        "email": "wyatt.felix@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#39",
            "addressLine1": "The Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Porbandar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 309814
        },
        "quantity": 267,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-15T01:12:27.854Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-18T01:12:27.854Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Wyatt",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#39, The Villas, Bairagarh, Porbandar, Gujarat. 309814"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000098",
        "customerName": "Titus McCall",
        "phoneNumber": "9067046183",
        "email": "titus.mccall@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#29",
            "addressLine1": "CityViews",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Navsari",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 157738
        },
        "quantity": 809,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-13T19:50:18.796Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-16T19:50:18.796Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Titus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 14,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#29, CityViews, Jahangirabad, Navsari, Gujarat. 157738"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000218",
        "customerName": "Daxton Hebert",
        "phoneNumber": "7133032862",
        "email": "daxton.hebert@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#37",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 732212
        },
        "quantity": 918,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-11T02:12:59.426Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-14T02:12:59.426Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Daxton",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#37, Town Place Apartments, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 732212"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000279",
        "customerName": "Fatima Barker",
        "phoneNumber": "6998495077",
        "email": "fatima.barker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "Etta Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 504290
        },
        "quantity": 160,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-08T05:44:45.575Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-11T05:44:45.575Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Fatima",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, Etta Apartments, Marvadi Road, Tezpur, Assam. 504290"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000085",
        "customerName": "Emely Monroe",
        "phoneNumber": "8553058843",
        "email": "emely.monroe@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#75",
            "addressLine1": "The Mill",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 193745
        },
        "quantity": 864,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-08T00:57:39.757Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-11T00:57:39.757Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Emely",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#75, The Mill, Shahpura, Tezpur, Assam. 193745"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000034",
        "customerName": "Marlon Barry",
        "phoneNumber": "9283985793",
        "email": "marlon.barry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#74",
            "addressLine1": "Timber Ridge Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Eluru",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 314838
        },
        "quantity": 824,
        "orderedDate": "2023-08-07T03:58:53.740Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-08-10T03:58:53.740Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marlon",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#74, Timber Ridge Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Eluru, Andhra Pradesh. 314838"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000425",
        "customerName": "Alondra Lynn",
        "phoneNumber": "9015928501",
        "email": "alondra.lynn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#45",
            "addressLine1": "Spectrum on Spring",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 652210
        },
        "quantity": 333,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-26T00:57:02.420Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-29T00:57:02.420Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alondra",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 37,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#45, Spectrum on Spring, Hamidia Road, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 652210"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000041",
        "customerName": "Anais Evans",
        "phoneNumber": "8086156332",
        "email": "anais.evans@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "Sun’s Rays Place",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 388006
        },
        "quantity": 331,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-25T23:46:43.282Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-28T23:46:43.282Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Anais",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, Sun’s Rays Place, Shahpura, Guwahati, Assam. 388006"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000036",
        "customerName": "Conor Ellis",
        "phoneNumber": "7058369023",
        "email": "conor.ellis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#61",
            "addressLine1": "Merril Willow Rental Co.",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Navsari",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 990370
        },
        "quantity": 239,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-24T22:14:19.200Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-27T22:14:19.200Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Conor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#61, Merril Willow Rental Co., Malviya Nagar, Navsari, Gujarat. 990370"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000475",
        "customerName": "Jamie Reyna",
        "phoneNumber": "9484958171",
        "email": "jamie.reyna@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#49",
            "addressLine1": "Village Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Dhuburi",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 281603
        },
        "quantity": 962,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-17T16:19:32.748Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-20T16:19:32.748Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jamie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 52,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#49, Village Villas, Kolar Road, Dhuburi, Assam. 281603"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000238",
        "customerName": "Roy Campbell",
        "phoneNumber": "9344589167",
        "email": "roy.campbell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "The Palm Springs",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 295295
        },
        "quantity": 908,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-16T08:50:32.814Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-19T08:50:32.814Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Roy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, The Palm Springs, Raisen Road, Dispur, Assam. 295295"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000407",
        "customerName": "Princess Cochran",
        "phoneNumber": "8033996149",
        "email": "princess.cochran@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#97",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 349839
        },
        "quantity": 678,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-14T12:46:48.568Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-17T12:46:48.568Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Princess",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#97, The Bend, Jawahar Chowk, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 349839"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000097",
        "customerName": "Quinn Rhodes",
        "phoneNumber": "8047652816",
        "email": "quinn.rhodes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#23",
            "addressLine1": "Vertex condos",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 532209
        },
        "quantity": 917,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-14T01:45:47.508Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-17T01:45:47.508Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Quinn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#23, Vertex condos, Indrapuri, New Delhi, Delhi. 532209"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000090",
        "customerName": "Fernando Orozco",
        "phoneNumber": "6173355367",
        "email": "fernando.orozco@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "Youth Motive",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 808654
        },
        "quantity": 998,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-12T07:57:59.130Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-15T07:57:59.130Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Fernando",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, Youth Motive, Bairagarh, Tinsukia, Assam. 808654"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000190",
        "customerName": "Stephen Bean",
        "phoneNumber": "9248553092",
        "email": "stephen.bean@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#64",
            "addressLine1": "Joyous Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 162562
        },
        "quantity": 547,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-09T19:56:44.319Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-12T19:56:44.319Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Stephen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#64, Joyous Homes, Malviya Nagar, Madgaon, Goa. 162562"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000273",
        "customerName": "Aitana Reid",
        "phoneNumber": "7855414504",
        "email": "aitana.reid@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 325842
        },
        "quantity": 701,
        "orderedDate": "2023-07-05T08:03:10.005Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-08T08:03:10.005Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aitana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, La Grande Maison, Indrapuri, Delhi, Delhi. 325842"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000492",
        "customerName": "Vihaan Pierce",
        "phoneNumber": "9653797143",
        "email": "vihaan.pierce@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#60",
            "addressLine1": "Ventura Ridge",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 137320
        },
        "quantity": 592,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-30T23:23:18.890Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-03T23:23:18.890Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Vihaan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 96,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#60, Ventura Ridge, Hoshangabad Road, Madgaon, Goa. 137320"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000242",
        "customerName": "Sawyer Beltran",
        "phoneNumber": "8726542094",
        "email": "sawyer.beltran@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "Carriage House",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Guntur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 996704
        },
        "quantity": 584,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-28T08:34:15.588Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-01T08:34:15.588Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sawyer",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, Carriage House, TT Nagar, Guntur, Andhra Pradesh. 996704"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000227",
        "customerName": "Grace Frost",
        "phoneNumber": "7858038659",
        "email": "grace.frost@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "EcoStay",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 588616
        },
        "quantity": 161,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-28T07:03:26.172Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-07-01T07:03:26.172Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Grace",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 58,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, EcoStay, Hamidia Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 588616"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000002",
        "customerName": "Dominik Fields",
        "phoneNumber": "9851403632",
        "email": "dominik.fields@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "Seaview Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Chandragiri",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 793648
        },
        "quantity": 695,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-24T20:07:36.415Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-27T20:07:36.415Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dominik",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 61,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, Seaview Apartments, Bairagarh, Chandragiri, Andhra Pradesh. 793648"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000489",
        "customerName": "Maryam Burke",
        "phoneNumber": "7854638333",
        "email": "maryam.burke@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#40",
            "addressLine1": "Eastern Suburbs",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 638419
        },
        "quantity": 993,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-19T17:19:14.017Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-22T17:19:14.017Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maryam",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 55,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#40, Eastern Suburbs, Govind Pura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 638419"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000404",
        "customerName": "Julius Douglas",
        "phoneNumber": "8108235788",
        "email": "julius.douglas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "Joyous Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Kandla",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 843302
        },
        "quantity": 801,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-16T08:12:10.829Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-19T08:12:10.829Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Julius",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, Joyous Homes, Hoshangabad Road, Kandla, Gujarat. 843302"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000403",
        "customerName": "Kara Lowe",
        "phoneNumber": "7967314198",
        "email": "kara.lowe@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#19",
            "addressLine1": "Luxury Lake",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 180628
        },
        "quantity": 318,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-11T19:30:29.237Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-14T19:30:29.237Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#19, Luxury Lake, Hamidia Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 180628"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000418",
        "customerName": "Jonas Goodwin",
        "phoneNumber": "8358220909",
        "email": "jonas.goodwin@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Vertex condos",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 459978
        },
        "quantity": 385,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-09T13:52:21.278Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-12T13:52:21.278Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jonas",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 97,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Vertex condos, TT Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 459978"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000080",
        "customerName": "Korbyn Blevins",
        "phoneNumber": "9339799197",
        "email": "korbyn.blevins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#27",
            "addressLine1": "Wells Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Saharsa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 891620
        },
        "quantity": 990,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-08T09:37:17.567Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-11T09:37:17.567Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Korbyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#27, Wells Place Apartments, Malviya Nagar, Saharsa, Bihar. 891620"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000024",
        "customerName": "Layne Felix",
        "phoneNumber": "6663640341",
        "email": "layne.felix@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "The Palm Springs",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Bihar Sharif",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 753544
        },
        "quantity": 825,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-05T06:56:45.178Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-08T06:56:45.178Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Layne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 43,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, The Palm Springs, Bairagarh, Bihar Sharif, Bihar. 753544"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000341",
        "customerName": "Kaliyah Wiggins",
        "phoneNumber": "8145913309",
        "email": "kaliyah.wiggins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#63",
            "addressLine1": "New House",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 127546
        },
        "quantity": 622,
        "orderedDate": "2023-06-03T19:25:33.877Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-06-06T19:25:33.877Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaliyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 68,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#63, New House, Jawahar Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi. 127546"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000433",
        "customerName": "Hanna Frost",
        "phoneNumber": "8991066516",
        "email": "hanna.frost@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#88",
            "addressLine1": "MiniPalais",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 345321
        },
        "quantity": 850,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-22T01:14:07.107Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-25T01:14:07.107Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hanna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 17,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#88, MiniPalais, Marvadi Road, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 345321"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000006",
        "customerName": "Leonardo Pierce",
        "phoneNumber": "7920034374",
        "email": "leonardo.pierce@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "House of Lords",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Saharsa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 285818
        },
        "quantity": 165,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-19T02:23:12.465Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-22T02:23:12.465Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leonardo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 55,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, House of Lords, Habib Ganj, Saharsa, Bihar. 285818"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000467",
        "customerName": "Clare McCoy",
        "phoneNumber": "6327270784",
        "email": "clare.mccoy@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "Concrete homes",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 509255
        },
        "quantity": 896,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-18T00:09:16.903Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-21T00:09:16.903Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Clare",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, Concrete homes, Govind Pura, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 509255"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000375",
        "customerName": "Halle Bartlett",
        "phoneNumber": "9715141399",
        "email": "halle.bartlett@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 670723
        },
        "quantity": 103,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-17T10:23:53.635Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-20T10:23:53.635Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Halle",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, Sunshine Apartments, Arera Colony, Madgaon, Goa. 670723"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000414",
        "customerName": "Marco Mayo",
        "phoneNumber": "7700311249",
        "email": "marco.mayo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "Exotic homes",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Bhilai",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 929690
        },
        "quantity": 147,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-16T20:20:57.345Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-19T20:20:57.345Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marco",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, Exotic homes, Raisen Road, Bhilai, Chhattisgarh. 929690"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000473",
        "customerName": "Gabriela Galindo",
        "phoneNumber": "8886314695",
        "email": "gabriela.galindo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Patan",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 941031
        },
        "quantity": 343,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-09T22:06:17.153Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-12T22:06:17.153Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Gabriela",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Jolly City, Jawahar Chowk, Patan, Gujarat. 941031"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000423",
        "customerName": "Sloan Garner",
        "phoneNumber": "8954106011",
        "email": "sloan.garner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#64",
            "addressLine1": "The Station",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 591416
        },
        "quantity": 942,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-08T02:41:50.297Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-11T02:41:50.297Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sloan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 50,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#64, The Station, Govind Pura, Kheda, Gujarat. 591416"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000200",
        "customerName": "Bellamy Drake",
        "phoneNumber": "7655475871",
        "email": "bellamy.drake@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Exotic homes",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 970706
        },
        "quantity": 657,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-04T01:29:44.425Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-07T01:29:44.425Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Bellamy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 58,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Exotic homes, Bairagarh, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 970706"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000088",
        "customerName": "Jamison Salinas",
        "phoneNumber": "9010964730",
        "email": "jamison.salinas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "Broadway Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Porbandar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 436141
        },
        "quantity": 664,
        "orderedDate": "2023-05-02T09:36:12.096Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-05T09:36:12.096Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jamison",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 78,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, Broadway Lofts, TT Nagar, Porbandar, Gujarat. 436141"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000127",
        "customerName": "Remington Weber",
        "phoneNumber": "9997031051",
        "email": "remington.weber@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#22",
            "addressLine1": "New House",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Adoni",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 463250
        },
        "quantity": 983,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-29T17:54:12.686Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-02T17:54:12.686Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Remington",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#22, New House, Peer Gate, Adoni, Andhra Pradesh. 463250"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000371",
        "customerName": "Kailani Branch",
        "phoneNumber": "8131509299",
        "email": "kailani.branch@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#21",
            "addressLine1": "Ray White Residential",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Bhilai",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 728865
        },
        "quantity": 981,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-29T13:52:05.619Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-02T13:52:05.619Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kailani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 79,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#21, Ray White Residential, Shahpura, Bhilai, Chhattisgarh. 728865"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000321",
        "customerName": "Wynter Watson",
        "phoneNumber": "7547254080",
        "email": "wynter.watson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "One Circular Quay",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 732132
        },
        "quantity": 530,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-29T04:24:25.422Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-05-02T04:24:25.422Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Wynter",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, One Circular Quay, Kolar Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 732132"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000379",
        "customerName": "Corinne Conley",
        "phoneNumber": "6641647499",
        "email": "corinne.conley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#59",
            "addressLine1": "Homes for all",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Siwan",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 275469
        },
        "quantity": 143,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-23T14:23:57.178Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-26T14:23:57.178Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Corinne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#59, Homes for all, Govind Pura, Siwan, Bihar. 275469"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000169",
        "customerName": "Laura Freeman",
        "phoneNumber": "6964979255",
        "email": "laura.freeman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "Silver House",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 226167
        },
        "quantity": 715,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-11T03:45:59.196Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-14T03:45:59.196Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Laura",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, Silver House, Marvadi Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 226167"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000311",
        "customerName": "Yasmin Mosley",
        "phoneNumber": "7304784895",
        "email": "yasmin.mosley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Vertex condos",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Jorhat",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 381162
        },
        "quantity": 621,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-06T16:48:52.254Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-09T16:48:52.254Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Yasmin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Vertex condos, Berasia Road, Jorhat, Assam. 381162"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000058",
        "customerName": "Rocky Sutton",
        "phoneNumber": "7478281103",
        "email": "rocky.sutton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#19",
            "addressLine1": "Homes for all",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Ahmadabad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 962207
        },
        "quantity": 383,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-02T08:48:31.429Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-05T08:48:31.429Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rocky",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 25,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#19, Homes for all, Malviya Nagar, Ahmadabad, Gujarat. 962207"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000132",
        "customerName": "Ahmir Spencer",
        "phoneNumber": "6580503122",
        "email": "ahmir.spencer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Wild Estates",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Samastipur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 731981
        },
        "quantity": 889,
        "orderedDate": "2023-04-02T07:44:12.806Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-05T07:44:12.806Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ahmir",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Wild Estates, TT Nagar, Samastipur, Bihar. 731981"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000259",
        "customerName": "Elizabeth Henry",
        "phoneNumber": "6528912775",
        "email": "elizabeth.henry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 688321
        },
        "quantity": 762,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-30T04:20:20.374Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-02T04:20:20.374Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Elizabeth",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, Jolly City, Peer Gate, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 688321"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000077",
        "customerName": "Penelope Warner",
        "phoneNumber": "6250529713",
        "email": "penelope.warner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#75",
            "addressLine1": "Cove Property",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 378527
        },
        "quantity": 574,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-29T12:27:10.043Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-04-01T12:27:10.043Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Penelope",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 85,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#75, Cove Property, Jawahar Chowk, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 378527"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000176",
        "customerName": "Andy Castillo",
        "phoneNumber": "7713551559",
        "email": "andy.castillo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 334911
        },
        "quantity": 980,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-14T08:34:54.405Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-17T08:34:54.405Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Andy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 54,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, City Dwellers, TT Nagar, Panaji, Goa. 334911"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000117",
        "customerName": "Frances Vasquez",
        "phoneNumber": "9364791112",
        "email": "frances.vasquez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Surf Rider Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 670143
        },
        "quantity": 224,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-14T02:44:29.971Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-17T02:44:29.971Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Frances",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 11,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Surf Rider Apartments, Hamidia Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 670143"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000301",
        "customerName": "Maeve Wagner",
        "phoneNumber": "9582746209",
        "email": "maeve.wagner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#85",
            "addressLine1": "ApHEARTments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 771624
        },
        "quantity": 988,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-13T12:13:58.929Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-16T12:13:58.929Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maeve",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#85, ApHEARTments, Marvadi Road, Delhi, Delhi. 771624"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000370",
        "customerName": "Caspian Wang",
        "phoneNumber": "8967509948",
        "email": "caspian.wang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "The City Block",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 902202
        },
        "quantity": 111,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-07T15:17:31.424Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-10T15:17:31.424Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Caspian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 49,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, The City Block, Raisen Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 902202"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000211",
        "customerName": "Mercy Simon",
        "phoneNumber": "9774262172",
        "email": "mercy.simon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Spectrum on Spring",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 283504
        },
        "quantity": 349,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-05T17:46:39.570Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-08T17:46:39.570Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mercy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 44,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Spectrum on Spring, Kolar Road, Dispur, Assam. 283504"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000026",
        "customerName": "Drake Bryant",
        "phoneNumber": "7304415882",
        "email": "drake.bryant@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#99",
            "addressLine1": "Lilli Midtown Flats",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 546652
        },
        "quantity": 388,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-04T11:53:17.241Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-07T11:53:17.241Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Drake",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 30,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#99, Lilli Midtown Flats, Bittan Market, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 546652"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000209",
        "customerName": "Rosie Nixon",
        "phoneNumber": "6449127479",
        "email": "rosie.nixon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "The Station",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 430233
        },
        "quantity": 938,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-01T20:46:00.509Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-04T20:46:00.509Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rosie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, The Station, Jawahar Chowk, Silchar, Assam. 430233"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000402",
        "customerName": "Ocean Harrell",
        "phoneNumber": "6594572658",
        "email": "ocean.harrell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#98",
            "addressLine1": "Harmony Park",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Bhuj",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 661570
        },
        "quantity": 352,
        "orderedDate": "2023-03-01T03:18:37.538Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-04T03:18:37.538Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ocean",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#98, Harmony Park, Habib Ganj, Bhuj, Gujarat. 661570"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000289",
        "customerName": "Paisleigh Blackwell",
        "phoneNumber": "8983828305",
        "email": "paisleigh.blackwell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Walkups",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 426044
        },
        "quantity": 473,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-27T03:47:20.629Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-03-02T03:47:20.629Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paisleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 11,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Town Place Walkups, Berasia Road, Delhi, Delhi. 426044"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000065",
        "customerName": "Marleigh Underwood",
        "phoneNumber": "6555851858",
        "email": "marleigh.underwood@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "Etta Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 589357
        },
        "quantity": 733,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-24T09:19:21.169Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-02-27T09:19:21.169Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 44,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, Etta Apartments, Sultania Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 589357"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000108",
        "customerName": "Solomon Bullock",
        "phoneNumber": "9782396644",
        "email": "solomon.bullock@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Peace apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 456044
        },
        "quantity": 511,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-20T06:00:11.080Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-02-23T06:00:11.080Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Solomon",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Peace apartments, Shivaji Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 456044"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000300",
        "customerName": "Trevor Wagner",
        "phoneNumber": "8351458597",
        "email": "trevor.wagner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 742522
        },
        "quantity": 589,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-06T11:21:23.476Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-02-09T11:21:23.476Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Trevor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 31,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, The Bend, Malviya Nagar, Panaji, Goa. 742522"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000053",
        "customerName": "Kalani Vang",
        "phoneNumber": "7962934692",
        "email": "kalani.vang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Greenway Court Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 380396
        },
        "quantity": 451,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-05T01:12:31.703Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-02-08T01:12:31.703Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kalani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 25,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Greenway Court Apartments, Indrapuri, New Delhi, Delhi. 380396"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000485",
        "customerName": "Carolyn Davenport",
        "phoneNumber": "7396836596",
        "email": "carolyn.davenport@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "The Jacks",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 862900
        },
        "quantity": 332,
        "orderedDate": "2023-02-02T01:27:07.930Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-02-05T01:27:07.930Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Carolyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 54,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, The Jacks, Arera Colony, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 862900"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000042",
        "customerName": "Elias Erickson",
        "phoneNumber": "9274323853",
        "email": "elias.erickson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Royal View",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 663595
        },
        "quantity": 585,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-28T04:53:59.514Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-31T04:53:59.514Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Elias",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Royal View, Shivaji Nagar, Tinsukia, Assam. 663595"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000265",
        "customerName": "Ryleigh Meza",
        "phoneNumber": "6673477891",
        "email": "ryleigh.meza@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Nature Custom",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 204895
        },
        "quantity": 811,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-24T00:36:53.760Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-27T00:36:53.760Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ryleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Nature Custom, Arera Colony, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 204895"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000406",
        "customerName": "Callen Browning",
        "phoneNumber": "9483817702",
        "email": "callen.browning@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#84",
            "addressLine1": "The Mill",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Adoni",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 492608
        },
        "quantity": 815,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-15T12:06:14.867Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-18T12:06:14.867Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Callen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#84, The Mill, Jahangirabad, Adoni, Andhra Pradesh. 492608"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000488",
        "customerName": "Koda Buchanan",
        "phoneNumber": "9727407282",
        "email": "koda.buchanan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#36",
            "addressLine1": "Life on the Green",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Jamnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 226402
        },
        "quantity": 204,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-14T10:32:34.155Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-17T10:32:34.155Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Koda",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#36, Life on the Green, Bittan Market, Jamnagar, Gujarat. 226402"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000500",
        "customerName": "Caiden Cuevas",
        "phoneNumber": "6395490345",
        "email": "caiden.cuevas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Park Central Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 848418
        },
        "quantity": 431,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-08T03:31:36.773Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-11T03:31:36.773Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Caiden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Park Central Apartments, MP Nagar, Kheda, Gujarat. 848418"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000054",
        "customerName": "Jimmy Fitzgerald",
        "phoneNumber": "8091314954",
        "email": "jimmy.fitzgerald@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 394577
        },
        "quantity": 321,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-06T13:31:16.837Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-09T13:31:16.837Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jimmy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Sunshine Apartments, Jahangirabad, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 394577"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000111",
        "customerName": "Adalynn Elliott",
        "phoneNumber": "8860706716",
        "email": "adalynn.elliott@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Anantapur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 752914
        },
        "quantity": 801,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-03T14:49:03.743Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-06T14:49:03.743Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Adalynn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Town Place Apartments, Arera Colony, Anantapur, Andhra Pradesh. 752914"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000399",
        "customerName": "Galilea Rios",
        "phoneNumber": "9643693483",
        "email": "galilea.rios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#16",
            "addressLine1": "WinterSpring Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 934598
        },
        "quantity": 572,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-02T06:58:32.182Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-05T06:58:32.182Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Galilea",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#16, WinterSpring Rental, Berasia Road, Delhi, Delhi. 934598"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000039",
        "customerName": "Kaydence Horn",
        "phoneNumber": "8745117495",
        "email": "kaydence.horn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#27",
            "addressLine1": "Concrete homes",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Pusa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 632027
        },
        "quantity": 551,
        "orderedDate": "2023-01-01T01:23:26.881Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-04T01:23:26.881Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaydence",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#27, Concrete homes, Peer Gate, Pusa, Bihar. 632027"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000358",
        "customerName": "Avery Maxwell",
        "phoneNumber": "9707497437",
        "email": "avery.maxwell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "Passion homes",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 849575
        },
        "quantity": 218,
        "orderedDate": "2022-12-30T11:56:38.753Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2023-01-02T11:56:38.753Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Avery",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, Passion homes, Habib Ganj, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 849575"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000441",
        "customerName": "Lilith Cantu",
        "phoneNumber": "9280249871",
        "email": "lilith.cantu@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#26",
            "addressLine1": "EcoStay",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 639211
        },
        "quantity": 446,
        "orderedDate": "2022-12-16T16:49:12.383Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-19T16:49:12.383Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lilith",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#26, EcoStay, Arera Colony, Panaji, Goa. 639211"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000150",
        "customerName": "Aydin Bender",
        "phoneNumber": "6908100551",
        "email": "aydin.bender@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#12",
            "addressLine1": "The Griffin",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 433995
        },
        "quantity": 782,
        "orderedDate": "2022-12-15T05:14:25.690Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-18T05:14:25.690Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aydin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 38,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#12, The Griffin, Raisen Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 433995"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000121",
        "customerName": "Mylah Jones",
        "phoneNumber": "6756495362",
        "email": "mylah.jones@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "The Twin Towers",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Jamnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 722582
        },
        "quantity": 196,
        "orderedDate": "2022-12-10T21:20:55.003Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-13T21:20:55.003Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mylah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, The Twin Towers, Jawahar Chowk, Jamnagar, Gujarat. 722582"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000314",
        "customerName": "Uriah Hutchinson",
        "phoneNumber": "9701194958",
        "email": "uriah.hutchinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#22",
            "addressLine1": "Elite Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Amreli",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 216447
        },
        "quantity": 888,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-30T17:58:00.249Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-03T17:58:00.249Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Uriah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#22, Elite Apartments, Habib Ganj, Amreli, Gujarat. 216447"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000417",
        "customerName": "Karsyn Gallegos",
        "phoneNumber": "6177754701",
        "email": "karsyn.gallegos@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 271367
        },
        "quantity": 353,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-30T07:36:41.045Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-03T07:36:41.045Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Karsyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Homely Villas, Sultania Road, Tezpur, Assam. 271367"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000267",
        "customerName": "Sylvia Duncan",
        "phoneNumber": "8501704619",
        "email": "sylvia.duncan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#98",
            "addressLine1": "Greenway Court Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Chittoor",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 417744
        },
        "quantity": 963,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-29T08:35:02.153Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-02T08:35:02.153Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sylvia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#98, Greenway Court Apartments, Berasia Road, Chittoor, Andhra Pradesh. 417744"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000207",
        "customerName": "Blaire Beasley",
        "phoneNumber": "6689344668",
        "email": "blaire.beasley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Elite Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 528632
        },
        "quantity": 785,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-29T03:40:38.939Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-12-02T03:40:38.939Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Blaire",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Elite Apartments, Indrapuri, Delhi, Delhi. 528632"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000210",
        "customerName": "Cory Sellers",
        "phoneNumber": "6893034971",
        "email": "cory.sellers@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#61",
            "addressLine1": "Stanley Park Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Khambhat",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 225787
        },
        "quantity": 816,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-24T22:01:51.111Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-27T22:01:51.111Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cory",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#61, Stanley Park Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Khambhat, Gujarat. 225787"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000376",
        "customerName": "Kace Steele",
        "phoneNumber": "7014886125",
        "email": "kace.steele@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#84",
            "addressLine1": "CappaCale Dale",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 520507
        },
        "quantity": 786,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-17T22:12:08.682Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-20T22:12:08.682Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kace",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#84, CappaCale Dale, Bairagarh, Panaji, Goa. 520507"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000235",
        "customerName": "Ella Mendoza",
        "phoneNumber": "7119003657",
        "email": "ella.mendoza@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#85",
            "addressLine1": "The Den",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Jorhat",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 194351
        },
        "quantity": 392,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-15T19:55:01.438Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-18T19:55:01.438Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ella",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#85, The Den, Marvadi Road, Jorhat, Assam. 194351"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000268",
        "customerName": "Avery Coffey",
        "phoneNumber": "8798772272",
        "email": "avery.coffey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#50",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Darbhanga",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 903688
        },
        "quantity": 267,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-14T02:22:52.933Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-17T02:22:52.933Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Avery",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#50, Sunshine Apartments, Bittan Market, Darbhanga, Bihar. 903688"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000427",
        "customerName": "Tori Decker",
        "phoneNumber": "8584067001",
        "email": "tori.decker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 901938
        },
        "quantity": 548,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-08T13:21:50.123Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-11T13:21:50.123Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tori",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, City Dwellers, Indrapuri, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 901938"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000383",
        "customerName": "Flora Estes",
        "phoneNumber": "8463715453",
        "email": "flora.estes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "Silver House",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 687508
        },
        "quantity": 491,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-06T17:20:52.206Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-09T17:20:52.206Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Flora",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 33,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, Silver House, Indrapuri, Delhi, Delhi. 687508"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000401",
        "customerName": "Katherine Sloan",
        "phoneNumber": "6365431365",
        "email": "katherine.sloan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#17",
            "addressLine1": "Wells Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 783391
        },
        "quantity": 909,
        "orderedDate": "2022-11-03T17:13:41.333Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-11-06T17:13:41.333Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Katherine",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 96,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#17, Wells Place Apartments, Govind Pura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 783391"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000324",
        "customerName": "Edwin Blair",
        "phoneNumber": "7096281568",
        "email": "edwin.blair@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#40",
            "addressLine1": "Apartment Partners",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 638794
        },
        "quantity": 559,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-27T20:38:11.960Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-30T20:38:11.960Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Edwin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#40, Apartment Partners, MP Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 638794"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000020",
        "customerName": "Edwin Day",
        "phoneNumber": "8501909093",
        "email": "edwin.day@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "New House",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 764968
        },
        "quantity": 886,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-23T23:56:45.994Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-26T23:56:45.994Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Edwin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 55,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, New House, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 764968"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000323",
        "customerName": "Genesis Schwartz",
        "phoneNumber": "9068092885",
        "email": "genesis.schwartz@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Seaview Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 853291
        },
        "quantity": 590,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-23T17:01:25.696Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-26T17:01:25.696Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Genesis",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 49,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Seaview Apartments, Marvadi Road, Delhi, Delhi. 853291"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000293",
        "customerName": "Lyric Mata",
        "phoneNumber": "9487424327",
        "email": "lyric.mata@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "Joyful Place",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Begusarai",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 692737
        },
        "quantity": 163,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-23T03:12:03.254Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-26T03:12:03.254Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lyric",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 29,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, Joyful Place, Hamidia Road, Begusarai, Bihar. 692737"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000244",
        "customerName": "Marvin Huerta",
        "phoneNumber": "8316560322",
        "email": "marvin.huerta@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "Rockwell",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Kakinada",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 729867
        },
        "quantity": 892,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-17T12:57:53.942Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-20T12:57:53.942Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marvin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 11,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, Rockwell, Bairagarh, Kakinada, Andhra Pradesh. 729867"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000322",
        "customerName": "Greyson Morris",
        "phoneNumber": "7458479770",
        "email": "greyson.morris@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Peace apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 132817
        },
        "quantity": 717,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-13T00:36:21.587Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-16T00:36:21.587Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Greyson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 39,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Peace apartments, Malviya Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 132817"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000145",
        "customerName": "Aileen Hampton",
        "phoneNumber": "8230329876",
        "email": "aileen.hampton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Newport Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 761752
        },
        "quantity": 448,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-11T08:35:02.035Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-14T08:35:02.035Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aileen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Newport Apartments, Kolar Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 761752"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000354",
        "customerName": "River Waller",
        "phoneNumber": "8430303611",
        "email": "river.waller@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Homes with peace",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Katihar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 930652
        },
        "quantity": 973,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-09T08:41:30.844Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-12T08:41:30.844Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "River",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 24,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Homes with peace, Bairagarh, Katihar, Bihar. 930652"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000266",
        "customerName": "Lucian Casey",
        "phoneNumber": "8680765258",
        "email": "lucian.casey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#86",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Place",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 313358
        },
        "quantity": 701,
        "orderedDate": "2022-10-03T04:19:17.620Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-06T04:19:17.620Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lucian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 10,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#86, Sunshine Place, Bairagarh, New Delhi, Delhi. 313358"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000082",
        "customerName": "Major Hughes",
        "phoneNumber": "6765405310",
        "email": "major.hughes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Luxury Lake",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 887648
        },
        "quantity": 670,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-29T09:58:33.225Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-10-02T09:58:33.225Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Major",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 19,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Luxury Lake, MP Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 887648"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000410",
        "customerName": "Braylen Sanchez",
        "phoneNumber": "6042318159",
        "email": "braylen.sanchez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#60",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 572247
        },
        "quantity": 628,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-27T21:17:52.250Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-30T21:17:52.250Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Braylen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 22,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#60, Jolly City, Malviya Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 572247"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000131",
        "customerName": "Noor Moyer",
        "phoneNumber": "6988404862",
        "email": "noor.moyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "The Palm Springs",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 988950
        },
        "quantity": 820,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-24T01:43:08.439Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-27T01:43:08.439Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Noor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, The Palm Springs, Sultania Road, Panaji, Goa. 988950"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000243",
        "customerName": "Kaydence Conley",
        "phoneNumber": "7575758816",
        "email": "kaydence.conley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Ahmadabad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 999583
        },
        "quantity": 298,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-17T22:18:15.335Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-20T22:18:15.335Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaydence",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, La Grande Maison, Arera Colony, Ahmadabad, Gujarat. 999583"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000050",
        "customerName": "Israel Vang",
        "phoneNumber": "9513655618",
        "email": "israel.vang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Ray White Residential",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Anantapur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 873085
        },
        "quantity": 302,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-14T22:38:54.507Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-17T22:38:54.507Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Israel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 46,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Ray White Residential, Habib Ganj, Anantapur, Andhra Pradesh. 873085"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000466",
        "customerName": "Kyler Glass",
        "phoneNumber": "6072192364",
        "email": "kyler.glass@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Newport Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 856359
        },
        "quantity": 748,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-12T17:43:47.285Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-15T17:43:47.285Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kyler",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 90,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Newport Apartments, Bittan Market, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 856359"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000184",
        "customerName": "Ares Romero",
        "phoneNumber": "8005270082",
        "email": "ares.romero@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "Cove Property",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 817020
        },
        "quantity": 664,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-10T21:25:46.227Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-13T21:25:46.227Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ares",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, Cove Property, Hoshangabad Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 817020"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000007",
        "customerName": "Arabella Palacios",
        "phoneNumber": "7197588224",
        "email": "arabella.palacios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "The Village View",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 597935
        },
        "quantity": 253,
        "orderedDate": "2022-09-06T13:37:26.898Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-09-09T13:37:26.898Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Arabella",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, The Village View, Hamidia Road, Delhi, Delhi. 597935"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000043",
        "customerName": "Sabrina Marshall",
        "phoneNumber": "7939566071",
        "email": "sabrina.marshall@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#83",
            "addressLine1": "The Griffin",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Dowlaiswaram",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 991438
        },
        "quantity": 853,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-26T12:46:09.470Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-29T12:46:09.470Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sabrina",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 30,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#83, The Griffin, Sultania Road, Dowlaiswaram, Andhra Pradesh. 991438"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000107",
        "customerName": "Jianna Barber",
        "phoneNumber": "7500936715",
        "email": "jianna.barber@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "One Circular Quay",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Dibrugarh",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 899891
        },
        "quantity": 809,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-14T08:47:32.364Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-17T08:47:32.364Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jianna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 17,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, One Circular Quay, Shahpura, Dibrugarh, Assam. 899891"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000170",
        "customerName": "Jayce York",
        "phoneNumber": "8094091474",
        "email": "jayce.york@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#49",
            "addressLine1": "Soft bed rentals",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Bettiah",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 725523
        },
        "quantity": 599,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-09T04:23:09.860Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-12T04:23:09.860Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jayce",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#49, Soft bed rentals, MP Nagar, Bettiah, Bihar. 725523"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000233",
        "customerName": "Elianna Conrad",
        "phoneNumber": "9895236349",
        "email": "elianna.conrad@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Peace Waters",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 798834
        },
        "quantity": 167,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-04T04:22:25.351Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-07T04:22:25.351Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Elianna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Peace Waters, Kolar Road, Panaji, Goa. 798834"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000333",
        "customerName": "Fiona Hardin",
        "phoneNumber": "7150866474",
        "email": "fiona.hardin@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#88",
            "addressLine1": "Paradise Palms",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 162846
        },
        "quantity": 234,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-03T15:03:10.373Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-06T15:03:10.373Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Fiona",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#88, Paradise Palms, Berasia Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 162846"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000450",
        "customerName": "Derrick Briggs",
        "phoneNumber": "8036843108",
        "email": "derrick.briggs@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#49",
            "addressLine1": "Skyline Condo",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 126793
        },
        "quantity": 419,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-03T00:29:46.768Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-06T00:29:46.768Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Derrick",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 35,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#49, Skyline Condo, Jahangirabad, Panaji, Goa. 126793"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000136",
        "customerName": "Edison Banks",
        "phoneNumber": "7865462999",
        "email": "edison.banks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Nagaon",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 570125
        },
        "quantity": 780,
        "orderedDate": "2022-08-03T00:16:47.631Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-08-06T00:16:47.631Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Edison",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, La Grande Maison, Bittan Market, Nagaon, Assam. 570125"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000315",
        "customerName": "Jamie Everett",
        "phoneNumber": "8139841122",
        "email": "jamie.everett@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "Tropicana Del Norte",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 972972
        },
        "quantity": 595,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-26T02:30:14.711Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-29T02:30:14.711Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jamie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, Tropicana Del Norte, Hamidia Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 972972"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000001",
        "customerName": "Miracle Booker",
        "phoneNumber": "7706860868",
        "email": "miracle.booker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "Peace apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 588844
        },
        "quantity": 411,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-25T04:29:07.334Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-28T04:29:07.334Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Miracle",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, Peace apartments, Arera Colony, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 588844"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000476",
        "customerName": "Reginald Watts",
        "phoneNumber": "6609400760",
        "email": "reginald.watts@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Guntur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 319614
        },
        "quantity": 257,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-20T20:12:52.973Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-23T20:12:52.973Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Reginald",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, Jolly City, Malviya Nagar, Guntur, Andhra Pradesh. 319614"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000310",
        "customerName": "Marvin Alfaro",
        "phoneNumber": "8686956849",
        "email": "marvin.alfaro@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#43",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Kurnool",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 204174
        },
        "quantity": 471,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-20T16:07:01.403Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-23T16:07:01.403Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marvin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 69,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#43, Homely Villas, Bairagarh, Kurnool, Andhra Pradesh. 204174"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000181",
        "customerName": "Violet Dean",
        "phoneNumber": "8624337797",
        "email": "violet.dean@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "The Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Dibrugarh",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 718229
        },
        "quantity": 260,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-20T14:31:14.413Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-23T14:31:14.413Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Violet",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 35,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, The Villas, Govind Pura, Dibrugarh, Assam. 718229"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000239",
        "customerName": "Addison Ali",
        "phoneNumber": "6870709002",
        "email": "addison.ali@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Wild Estates",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 346677
        },
        "quantity": 114,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-14T15:14:12.681Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-17T15:14:12.681Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Addison",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 25,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Wild Estates, Shahpura, Madgaon, Goa. 346677"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000017",
        "customerName": "Kimber Guevara",
        "phoneNumber": "8367181892",
        "email": "kimber.guevara@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "Shoebox",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 697392
        },
        "quantity": 136,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-12T16:59:37.466Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-15T16:59:37.466Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kimber",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 59,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, Shoebox, Peer Gate, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 697392"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000387",
        "customerName": "Skyler Mullins",
        "phoneNumber": "9344006364",
        "email": "skyler.mullins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "The River",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 261504
        },
        "quantity": 507,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-09T17:06:16.909Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-12T17:06:16.909Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Skyler",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, The River, Kolar Road, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 261504"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000064",
        "customerName": "Lennox McClain",
        "phoneNumber": "7286690988",
        "email": "lennox.mcclain@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "Ventura Ridge",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 971869
        },
        "quantity": 447,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-06T00:22:15.719Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-09T00:22:15.719Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lennox",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, Ventura Ridge, Shivaji Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 971869"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000248",
        "customerName": "Ivan Patterson",
        "phoneNumber": "7841595903",
        "email": "ivan.patterson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Timber Ridge Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 905561
        },
        "quantity": 805,
        "orderedDate": "2022-07-02T06:18:54.842Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-05T06:18:54.842Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ivan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 59,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Timber Ridge Apartments, Habib Ganj, Delhi, Delhi. 905561"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000089",
        "customerName": "Royalty Fleming",
        "phoneNumber": "7811970466",
        "email": "royalty.fleming@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#88",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 669278
        },
        "quantity": 936,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-28T18:19:38.639Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-07-01T18:19:38.639Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Royalty",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#88, Jolly City, Arera Colony, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 669278"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000147",
        "customerName": "Estrella Donovan",
        "phoneNumber": "6632894483",
        "email": "estrella.donovan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#97",
            "addressLine1": "East Side Living",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 366538
        },
        "quantity": 120,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-20T05:09:14.301Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-23T05:09:14.301Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Estrella",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#97, East Side Living, Marvadi Road, Dispur, Assam. 366538"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000191",
        "customerName": "Jenesis Weber",
        "phoneNumber": "6832322646",
        "email": "jenesis.weber@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "Standard At Legacy",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 212707
        },
        "quantity": 806,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-19T22:33:08.875Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-22T22:33:08.875Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jenesis",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, Standard At Legacy, Marvadi Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 212707"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000482",
        "customerName": "Trace Bowen",
        "phoneNumber": "6239241348",
        "email": "trace.bowen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#64",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Nagaon",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 736386
        },
        "quantity": 839,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-18T17:48:06.294Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-21T17:48:06.294Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Trace",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 45,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#64, Sunshine Apartments, Shivaji Nagar, Nagaon, Assam. 736386"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000374",
        "customerName": "Prince Medrano",
        "phoneNumber": "6951051719",
        "email": "prince.medrano@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#12",
            "addressLine1": "Greenway Court Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Raipur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 735007
        },
        "quantity": 704,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-18T01:40:46.291Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-21T01:40:46.291Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Prince",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#12, Greenway Court Apartments, TT Nagar, Raipur, Chhattisgarh. 735007"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000297",
        "customerName": "Lilly Sparks",
        "phoneNumber": "9299667876",
        "email": "lilly.sparks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "Joyous Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Madhubani",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 743952
        },
        "quantity": 445,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-15T22:04:30.687Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-18T22:04:30.687Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lilly",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, Joyous Homes, Jawahar Chowk, Madhubani, Bihar. 743952"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000363",
        "customerName": "Zara Cain",
        "phoneNumber": "9487658152",
        "email": "zara.cain@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#88",
            "addressLine1": "Royal View",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 101166
        },
        "quantity": 820,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-12T17:27:19.037Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-15T17:27:19.037Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#88, Royal View, Jawahar Chowk, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 101166"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000173",
        "customerName": "Anika Hendricks",
        "phoneNumber": "6941225905",
        "email": "anika.hendricks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "The River",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 143262
        },
        "quantity": 171,
        "orderedDate": "2022-06-01T21:29:29.944Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-06-04T21:29:29.944Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Anika",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, The River, Shahpura, Kheda, Gujarat. 143262"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000213",
        "customerName": "Heaven Haynes",
        "phoneNumber": "9391292303",
        "email": "heaven.haynes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#45",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Sivasagar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 283794
        },
        "quantity": 315,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-27T01:29:05.524Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-30T01:29:05.524Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Heaven",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#45, City Dwellers, Marvadi Road, Sivasagar, Assam. 283794"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000189",
        "customerName": "Macy Barnett",
        "phoneNumber": "7935880196",
        "email": "macy.barnett@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#19",
            "addressLine1": "Luxury Lake",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 706386
        },
        "quantity": 385,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-24T20:46:38.989Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-27T20:46:38.989Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Macy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#19, Luxury Lake, Kolar Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 706386"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000319",
        "customerName": "Camille Pittman",
        "phoneNumber": "7505743459",
        "email": "camille.pittman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "GreenHexa Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Yemmiganur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 335628
        },
        "quantity": 436,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-19T18:25:48.176Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-22T18:25:48.176Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Camille",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 30,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, GreenHexa Realty Rental, Jawahar Chowk, Yemmiganur, Andhra Pradesh. 335628"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000018",
        "customerName": "Tommy Jimenez",
        "phoneNumber": "7118489247",
        "email": "tommy.jimenez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Darling Building",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 802877
        },
        "quantity": 482,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-19T12:46:17.967Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-22T12:46:17.967Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tommy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Darling Building, Raisen Road, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 802877"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000138",
        "customerName": "Armando Stein",
        "phoneNumber": "7464125046",
        "email": "armando.stein@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "Platinum Oaks",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 300971
        },
        "quantity": 839,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-19T02:11:32.701Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-22T02:11:32.701Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Armando",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, Platinum Oaks, Habib Ganj, Madgaon, Goa. 300971"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000459",
        "customerName": "Ila Adams",
        "phoneNumber": "7753057336",
        "email": "ila.adams@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#83",
            "addressLine1": "Platinum Oaks",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 574158
        },
        "quantity": 506,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-19T00:36:16.149Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-22T00:36:16.149Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ila",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 61,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#83, Platinum Oaks, Shahpura, Tezpur, Assam. 574158"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000320",
        "customerName": "Valentino Warner",
        "phoneNumber": "6415005495",
        "email": "valentino.warner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 684804
        },
        "quantity": 610,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-19T00:32:36.293Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-22T00:32:36.293Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Valentino",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 19,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, City Dwellers, Koh E Fiza, Guwahati, Assam. 684804"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000198",
        "customerName": "Beau Herman",
        "phoneNumber": "8139878187",
        "email": "beau.herman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#23",
            "addressLine1": "Ideal homes",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Begusarai",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 874613
        },
        "quantity": 163,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-18T16:06:20.993Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-21T16:06:20.993Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Beau",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#23, Ideal homes, TT Nagar, Begusarai, Bihar. 874613"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000133",
        "customerName": "Alyssa McMillan",
        "phoneNumber": "7787884115",
        "email": "alyssa.mcmillan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Lilli Midtown Flats",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 762440
        },
        "quantity": 476,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-13T18:14:37.228Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-16T18:14:37.228Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alyssa",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 45,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Lilli Midtown Flats, Arera Colony, Madgaon, Goa. 762440"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000460",
        "customerName": "Hudson Sanders",
        "phoneNumber": "9664759604",
        "email": "hudson.sanders@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#72",
            "addressLine1": "Park Place",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 243825
        },
        "quantity": 907,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-05T21:47:35.168Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-08T21:47:35.168Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hudson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#72, Park Place, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 243825"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000419",
        "customerName": "Shiloh Villarreal",
        "phoneNumber": "7876519057",
        "email": "shiloh.villarreal@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "CityViews",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Bettiah",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 220754
        },
        "quantity": 396,
        "orderedDate": "2022-05-03T18:00:45.369Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-05-06T18:00:45.369Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Shiloh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, CityViews, Arera Colony, Bettiah, Bihar. 220754"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000096",
        "customerName": "Jefferson James",
        "phoneNumber": "8427977131",
        "email": "jefferson.james@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#82",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 174691
        },
        "quantity": 740,
        "orderedDate": "2022-04-08T18:02:01.843Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-04-11T18:02:01.843Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jefferson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#82, Homely Villas, Hoshangabad Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 174691"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000464",
        "customerName": "Leonel Mann",
        "phoneNumber": "8834980385",
        "email": "leonel.mann@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "Merril Willow Rental Co.",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 976910
        },
        "quantity": 551,
        "orderedDate": "2022-04-08T00:12:07.124Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-04-11T00:12:07.124Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leonel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, Merril Willow Rental Co., Bairagarh, Delhi, Delhi. 976910"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000100",
        "customerName": "Atticus Mendoza",
        "phoneNumber": "8597454672",
        "email": "atticus.mendoza@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#92",
            "addressLine1": "Elite Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Barauni",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 744115
        },
        "quantity": 358,
        "orderedDate": "2022-04-07T12:12:39.556Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-04-10T12:12:39.556Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Atticus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#92, Elite Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Barauni, Bihar. 744115"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000331",
        "customerName": "Demi Macias",
        "phoneNumber": "6282853049",
        "email": "demi.macias@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "Surf Rider Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Rajkot",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 952206
        },
        "quantity": 635,
        "orderedDate": "2022-04-04T19:42:01.889Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-04-07T19:42:01.889Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Demi",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 78,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, Surf Rider Apartments, Arera Colony, Rajkot, Gujarat. 952206"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000312",
        "customerName": "Rayden Edwards",
        "phoneNumber": "6014114461",
        "email": "rayden.edwards@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "CityViews",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 455549
        },
        "quantity": 878,
        "orderedDate": "2022-04-03T14:48:52.057Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-04-06T14:48:52.057Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rayden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, CityViews, Bittan Market, Panaji, Goa. 455549"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000327",
        "customerName": "Liliana Spence",
        "phoneNumber": "8437571745",
        "email": "liliana.spence@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#96",
            "addressLine1": "House of Lords",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Bhavnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 990920
        },
        "quantity": 345,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-25T04:32:23.085Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-28T04:32:23.085Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Liliana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 74,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#96, House of Lords, Shahpura, Bhavnagar, Gujarat. 990920"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000395",
        "customerName": "Haylee Patterson",
        "phoneNumber": "8309278066",
        "email": "haylee.patterson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "The Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 830367
        },
        "quantity": 425,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-23T11:45:51.354Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-26T11:45:51.354Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Haylee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 93,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, The Villas, Sultania Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 830367"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000003",
        "customerName": "Annie Palacios",
        "phoneNumber": "8348516448",
        "email": "annie.palacios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "Apartment Partners",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Srikakulam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 618492
        },
        "quantity": 739,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-19T11:55:33.998Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-22T11:55:33.998Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Annie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, Apartment Partners, Berasia Road, Srikakulam, Andhra Pradesh. 618492"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000405",
        "customerName": "Aniyah Norton",
        "phoneNumber": "7250122507",
        "email": "aniyah.norton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#17",
            "addressLine1": "Standard At Legacy",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 608765
        },
        "quantity": 487,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-15T18:16:13.039Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-18T18:16:13.039Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aniyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#17, Standard At Legacy, Indrapuri, Silchar, Assam. 608765"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000453",
        "customerName": "Katalina Cross",
        "phoneNumber": "9555716993",
        "email": "katalina.cross@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#63",
            "addressLine1": "Wild Estates",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Okha",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 535425
        },
        "quantity": 340,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-14T06:19:05.259Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-17T06:19:05.259Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Katalina",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#63, Wild Estates, Kolar Road, Okha, Gujarat. 535425"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000365",
        "customerName": "Milan Terry",
        "phoneNumber": "8531274459",
        "email": "milan.terry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Useful Units",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Bhuj",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 930994
        },
        "quantity": 819,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-11T20:03:47.575Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-14T20:03:47.575Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Milan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Useful Units, Kolar Road, Bhuj, Gujarat. 930994"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000206",
        "customerName": "Erick Glenn",
        "phoneNumber": "7874051308",
        "email": "erick.glenn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "Grand at the Dominion",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 258346
        },
        "quantity": 689,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-08T06:10:59.835Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-11T06:10:59.835Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Erick",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, Grand at the Dominion, Hoshangabad Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 258346"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000158",
        "customerName": "Oscar Livingston",
        "phoneNumber": "8772480666",
        "email": "oscar.livingston@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Nature Custom",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 343921
        },
        "quantity": 122,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-06T13:47:03.959Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-09T13:47:03.959Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Oscar",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 85,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Nature Custom, Bittan Market, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 343921"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000366",
        "customerName": "Armani Terry",
        "phoneNumber": "7626755503",
        "email": "armani.terry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#26",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 656603
        },
        "quantity": 198,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-06T04:37:35.995Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-09T04:37:35.995Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Armani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#26, Jolly City, Malviya Nagar, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 656603"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000122",
        "customerName": "William Steele",
        "phoneNumber": "6032450641",
        "email": "william.steele@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#59",
            "addressLine1": "The Niche Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Madhubani",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 895738
        },
        "quantity": 770,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-06T01:31:52.633Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-09T01:31:52.633Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "William",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#59, The Niche Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Madhubani, Bihar. 895738"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000496",
        "customerName": "Aden Bradford",
        "phoneNumber": "6738009263",
        "email": "aden.bradford@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Canyon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Bhuj",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 968313
        },
        "quantity": 705,
        "orderedDate": "2022-03-04T09:41:16.093Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-03-07T09:41:16.093Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 39,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, Hillside Canyon Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Bhuj, Gujarat. 968313"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000226",
        "customerName": "Aden Ramirez",
        "phoneNumber": "7934241487",
        "email": "aden.ramirez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "Paradise Palms",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Adoni",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 503625
        },
        "quantity": 822,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-25T16:19:09.681Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-28T16:19:09.681Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, Paradise Palms, Habib Ganj, Adoni, Andhra Pradesh. 503625"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000124",
        "customerName": "Uriel Young",
        "phoneNumber": "7737855136",
        "email": "uriel.young@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Shoebox",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 145465
        },
        "quantity": 149,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-25T09:02:44.832Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-28T09:02:44.832Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Uriel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Shoebox, Malviya Nagar, Madgaon, Goa. 145465"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000071",
        "customerName": "Skylar Sparks",
        "phoneNumber": "9762088343",
        "email": "skylar.sparks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 501930
        },
        "quantity": 103,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-21T05:20:00.688Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-24T05:20:00.688Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Skylar",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, The Bend, Govind Pura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 501930"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000397",
        "customerName": "Lauryn Watkins",
        "phoneNumber": "8335967344",
        "email": "lauryn.watkins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Junagadh",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 919962
        },
        "quantity": 165,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-19T20:06:16.236Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-22T20:06:16.236Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lauryn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 38,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, Hillside Apartments, Arera Colony, Junagadh, Gujarat. 919962"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000445",
        "customerName": "Maisie Stanley",
        "phoneNumber": "7702336988",
        "email": "maisie.stanley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Shoebox",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 588855
        },
        "quantity": 725,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-15T20:35:32.168Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-18T20:35:32.168Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maisie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Shoebox, Govind Pura, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 588855"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000286",
        "customerName": "Alan Clark",
        "phoneNumber": "7283031667",
        "email": "alan.clark@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "Park Central Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 835760
        },
        "quantity": 776,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-12T06:11:56.303Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-15T06:11:56.303Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, Park Central Apartments, TT Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 835760"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000463",
        "customerName": "Meghan Shelton",
        "phoneNumber": "7052103603",
        "email": "meghan.shelton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#99",
            "addressLine1": "Safe Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 491532
        },
        "quantity": 592,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-11T07:25:17.263Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-14T07:25:17.263Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Meghan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#99, Safe Homes, Arera Colony, Delhi, Delhi. 491532"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000201",
        "customerName": "Jayleen Lee",
        "phoneNumber": "6764844226",
        "email": "jayleen.lee@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "RealBond Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Buxar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 865292
        },
        "quantity": 946,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-08T04:45:28.241Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-11T04:45:28.241Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jayleen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, RealBond Realty Rental, Berasia Road, Buxar, Bihar. 865292"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000346",
        "customerName": "Genesis Blankenship",
        "phoneNumber": "8217171178",
        "email": "genesis.blankenship@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#40",
            "addressLine1": "Wild Estates",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 225840
        },
        "quantity": 199,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-06T12:50:23.629Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-09T12:50:23.629Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Genesis",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#40, Wild Estates, MP Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 225840"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000478",
        "customerName": "Ford West",
        "phoneNumber": "9195175631",
        "email": "ford.west@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#41",
            "addressLine1": "Ray White Residential",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 191476
        },
        "quantity": 168,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-06T10:36:31.368Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-09T10:36:31.368Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ford",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 29,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#41, Ray White Residential, MP Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 191476"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000140",
        "customerName": "Tripp Jaramillo",
        "phoneNumber": "9930674047",
        "email": "tripp.jaramillo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#13",
            "addressLine1": "Homes with peace",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Dhuburi",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 851847
        },
        "quantity": 211,
        "orderedDate": "2022-02-02T23:42:41.715Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-02-05T23:42:41.715Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tripp",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#13, Homes with peace, Hoshangabad Road, Dhuburi, Assam. 851847"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000009",
        "customerName": "Kiana Beltran",
        "phoneNumber": "8399596937",
        "email": "kiana.beltran@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "The Dorm Room",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 295949
        },
        "quantity": 837,
        "orderedDate": "2022-01-16T21:04:56.999Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-19T21:04:56.999Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kiana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, The Dorm Room, Indrapuri, Delhi, Delhi. 295949"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000146",
        "customerName": "Hank Dyer",
        "phoneNumber": "9697449714",
        "email": "hank.dyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Concrete homes",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Dehri",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 883775
        },
        "quantity": 214,
        "orderedDate": "2022-01-15T15:35:15.103Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-18T15:35:15.103Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hank",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Concrete homes, Malviya Nagar, Dehri, Bihar. 883775"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000183",
        "customerName": "Myla Carson",
        "phoneNumber": "9949025112",
        "email": "myla.carson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#86",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Katihar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 770565
        },
        "quantity": 212,
        "orderedDate": "2022-01-12T22:37:20.649Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-15T22:37:20.649Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Myla",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 10,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#86, Hillside Apartments, Hamidia Road, Katihar, Bihar. 770565"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000205",
        "customerName": "Addilynn Luna",
        "phoneNumber": "7098936210",
        "email": "addilynn.luna@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "CityViews",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 987940
        },
        "quantity": 244,
        "orderedDate": "2022-01-10T06:54:06.201Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-13T06:54:06.201Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Addilynn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 97,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, CityViews, Hamidia Road, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 987940"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000385",
        "customerName": "Mckenna Romero",
        "phoneNumber": "6587570071",
        "email": "mckenna.romero@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "Ventura Ridge",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 146194
        },
        "quantity": 206,
        "orderedDate": "2022-01-04T03:40:45.449Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-07T03:40:45.449Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mckenna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, Ventura Ridge, Jawahar Chowk, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 146194"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000095",
        "customerName": "Oaklee Sawyer",
        "phoneNumber": "9290820690",
        "email": "oaklee.sawyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "Harvest Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Munger",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 737796
        },
        "quantity": 879,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-30T23:39:09.797Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2022-01-02T23:39:09.797Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Oaklee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, Harvest Lofts, Hamidia Road, Munger, Bihar. 737796"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000021",
        "customerName": "Hayden Shannon",
        "phoneNumber": "6134972235",
        "email": "hayden.shannon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "The Den",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 686831
        },
        "quantity": 230,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-26T17:28:20.715Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-29T17:28:20.715Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hayden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 24,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, The Den, Sultania Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 686831"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000430",
        "customerName": "Zander House",
        "phoneNumber": "9474558675",
        "email": "zander.house@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#45",
            "addressLine1": "Seaview Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 458815
        },
        "quantity": 964,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-23T18:11:49.940Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-26T18:11:49.940Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zander",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#45, Seaview Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Madgaon, Goa. 458815"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000025",
        "customerName": "Paisleigh Sparks",
        "phoneNumber": "7004756526",
        "email": "paisleigh.sparks@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "Wild Estates",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 788032
        },
        "quantity": 310,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-20T14:04:32.080Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-23T14:04:32.080Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paisleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, Wild Estates, Berasia Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 788032"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000177",
        "customerName": "Eva Anderson",
        "phoneNumber": "8399889346",
        "email": "eva.anderson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#86",
            "addressLine1": "Blue Ribbon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Begusarai",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 976311
        },
        "quantity": 503,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-19T20:51:01.211Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-22T20:51:01.211Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eva",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#86, Blue Ribbon Apartments, Arera Colony, Begusarai, Bihar. 976311"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000271",
        "customerName": "Heaven Heath",
        "phoneNumber": "8311900890",
        "email": "heaven.heath@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "The Jacks",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 743775
        },
        "quantity": 910,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-18T17:54:21.464Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-21T17:54:21.464Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Heaven",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, The Jacks, Hamidia Road, Delhi, Delhi. 743775"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000454",
        "customerName": "Fabian Trevino",
        "phoneNumber": "7152976802",
        "email": "fabian.trevino@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "Lilli Midtown Flats",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 711351
        },
        "quantity": 616,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-13T01:29:43.580Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-16T01:29:43.580Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Fabian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 90,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, Lilli Midtown Flats, Malviya Nagar, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 711351"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000362",
        "customerName": "Shiloh Carroll",
        "phoneNumber": "7102456575",
        "email": "shiloh.carroll@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Sun’s Rays Place",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 886137
        },
        "quantity": 307,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-12T13:16:26.289Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-15T13:16:26.289Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Shiloh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 87,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Sun’s Rays Place, Jahangirabad, Delhi, Delhi. 886137"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000422",
        "customerName": "Ramon Mathews",
        "phoneNumber": "6676946080",
        "email": "ramon.mathews@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Tropicana Del Norte",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 303330
        },
        "quantity": 529,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-05T09:58:38.575Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-08T09:58:38.575Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ramon",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Tropicana Del Norte, Bittan Market, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 303330"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000230",
        "customerName": "Israel Hancock",
        "phoneNumber": "9041576155",
        "email": "israel.hancock@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "MasterGlory",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 896356
        },
        "quantity": 992,
        "orderedDate": "2021-12-03T10:15:20.500Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-12-06T10:15:20.500Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Israel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 45,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, MasterGlory, Jahangirabad, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 896356"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000420",
        "customerName": "Nikolai Simon",
        "phoneNumber": "6545911993",
        "email": "nikolai.simon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#76",
            "addressLine1": "Grand at the Dominion",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Gaya",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 892846
        },
        "quantity": 960,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-26T20:01:52.752Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-29T20:01:52.752Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nikolai",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 38,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#76, Grand at the Dominion, Bairagarh, Gaya, Bihar. 892846"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000055",
        "customerName": "Marlee Person",
        "phoneNumber": "7518739504",
        "email": "marlee.person@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#26",
            "addressLine1": "CappaCale Dale",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 157074
        },
        "quantity": 563,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-21T18:24:59.142Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-24T18:24:59.142Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marlee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#26, CappaCale Dale, Jawahar Chowk, Madgaon, Goa. 157074"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000413",
        "customerName": "Esme Klein",
        "phoneNumber": "7971552483",
        "email": "esme.klein@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#74",
            "addressLine1": "One Eighties Residences",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Bettiah",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 450886
        },
        "quantity": 776,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-18T20:48:45.230Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-21T20:48:45.230Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Esme",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 76,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#74, One Eighties Residences, Peer Gate, Bettiah, Bihar. 450886"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000330",
        "customerName": "Ocean Leonard",
        "phoneNumber": "8759365014",
        "email": "ocean.leonard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "The Dorm Room",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 925144
        },
        "quantity": 277,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-12T08:17:07.591Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-15T08:17:07.591Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ocean",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 68,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, The Dorm Room, TT Nagar, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 925144"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000106",
        "customerName": "Zaire Benjamin",
        "phoneNumber": "8195299934",
        "email": "zaire.benjamin@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 364277
        },
        "quantity": 482,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-07T03:41:18.222Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-10T03:41:18.222Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zaire",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, City Dwellers, Raisen Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 364277"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000386",
        "customerName": "Bryson Malone",
        "phoneNumber": "9581134880",
        "email": "bryson.malone@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "Etta Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 311085
        },
        "quantity": 965,
        "orderedDate": "2021-11-02T03:21:17.311Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-05T03:21:17.311Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Bryson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, Etta Apartments, Koh E Fiza, Delhi, Delhi. 311085"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000294",
        "customerName": "Ray Matthews",
        "phoneNumber": "8977661885",
        "email": "ray.matthews@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "Wells Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 993219
        },
        "quantity": 308,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-29T11:01:53.719Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-11-01T11:01:53.719Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ray",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 50,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, Wells Place Apartments, Hoshangabad Road, Kheda, Gujarat. 993219"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000093",
        "customerName": "Nora Woods",
        "phoneNumber": "8699187419",
        "email": "nora.woods@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#56",
            "addressLine1": "Exotic homes",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Jamnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 986193
        },
        "quantity": 627,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-28T22:55:21.829Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-31T22:55:21.829Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nora",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#56, Exotic homes, Govind Pura, Jamnagar, Gujarat. 986193"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000369",
        "customerName": "Aniyah Roach",
        "phoneNumber": "7785476691",
        "email": "aniyah.roach@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Srikakulam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 497880
        },
        "quantity": 547,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-28T20:42:53.100Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-31T20:42:53.100Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aniyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, Jolly City, Peer Gate, Srikakulam, Andhra Pradesh. 497880"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000325",
        "customerName": "Frances Wolfe",
        "phoneNumber": "8183634153",
        "email": "frances.wolfe@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Gaya",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 272085
        },
        "quantity": 311,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-28T17:17:23.670Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-31T17:17:23.670Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Frances",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Town Place Apartments, Peer Gate, Gaya, Bihar. 272085"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000456",
        "customerName": "Gunnar Harrington",
        "phoneNumber": "6652693394",
        "email": "gunnar.harrington@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "Carriage House",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 530425
        },
        "quantity": 306,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-27T14:39:34.316Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-30T14:39:34.316Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Gunnar",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 46,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, Carriage House, MP Nagar, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 530425"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000421",
        "customerName": "Kalani Kline",
        "phoneNumber": "6675581169",
        "email": "kalani.kline@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "Elite Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Bodh Gaya",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 905336
        },
        "quantity": 596,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-25T14:46:16.743Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-28T14:46:16.743Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kalani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, Elite Apartments, Berasia Road, Bodh Gaya, Bihar. 905336"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000035",
        "customerName": "Waverly Lin",
        "phoneNumber": "6652270241",
        "email": "waverly.lin@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Safe Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 258608
        },
        "quantity": 200,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-17T23:00:34.516Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-20T23:00:34.516Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Waverly",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 46,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Safe Homes, Kolar Road, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 258608"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000220",
        "customerName": "Zahir Williams",
        "phoneNumber": "6794548519",
        "email": "zahir.williams@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#96",
            "addressLine1": "House of Lords",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 861322
        },
        "quantity": 665,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-14T03:04:31.683Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-17T03:04:31.683Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zahir",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#96, House of Lords, TT Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 861322"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000149",
        "customerName": "Marina Hanna",
        "phoneNumber": "8266153049",
        "email": "marina.hanna@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Royal View",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 689817
        },
        "quantity": 775,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-13T07:59:31.215Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-16T07:59:31.215Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marina",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Royal View, Peer Gate, Madgaon, Goa. 689817"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000372",
        "customerName": "Keenan Smith",
        "phoneNumber": "8817307196",
        "email": "keenan.smith@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#68",
            "addressLine1": "Nature Custom",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Dinapur Nizamat",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 405109
        },
        "quantity": 597,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-11T17:35:35.173Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-14T17:35:35.173Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Keenan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#68, Nature Custom, Shivaji Nagar, Dinapur Nizamat, Bihar. 405109"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000134",
        "customerName": "Rocky Gilbert",
        "phoneNumber": "8705217038",
        "email": "rocky.gilbert@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#29",
            "addressLine1": "Ample Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 629837
        },
        "quantity": 472,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-06T20:27:03.630Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-09T20:27:03.630Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rocky",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#29, Ample Apartments, Bairagarh, New Delhi, Delhi. 629837"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000256",
        "customerName": "Marcus Henson",
        "phoneNumber": "8550275357",
        "email": "marcus.henson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#85",
            "addressLine1": "Royal View",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 278612
        },
        "quantity": 509,
        "orderedDate": "2021-10-03T14:21:25.397Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-10-06T14:21:25.397Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marcus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#85, Royal View, Malviya Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 278612"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000447",
        "customerName": "Ariyah Gillespie",
        "phoneNumber": "8304112115",
        "email": "ariyah.gillespie@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#60",
            "addressLine1": "Peace Waters",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 824844
        },
        "quantity": 259,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-26T17:57:16.003Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-29T17:57:16.003Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ariyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 61,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#60, Peace Waters, Hamidia Road, Madgaon, Goa. 824844"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000400",
        "customerName": "Israel Stevens",
        "phoneNumber": "9436870640",
        "email": "israel.stevens@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Joyful Place",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Amreli",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 904144
        },
        "quantity": 818,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-26T05:09:26.924Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-29T05:09:26.924Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Israel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Joyful Place, Bittan Market, Amreli, Gujarat. 904144"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000278",
        "customerName": "Flynn Fleming",
        "phoneNumber": "9704102013",
        "email": "flynn.fleming@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#37",
            "addressLine1": "Ventura Ridge",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Hajipur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 929454
        },
        "quantity": 452,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-24T14:11:46.544Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-27T14:11:46.544Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Flynn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#37, Ventura Ridge, Malviya Nagar, Hajipur, Bihar. 929454"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000384",
        "customerName": "Hakeem Howell",
        "phoneNumber": "7513368221",
        "email": "hakeem.howell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Soft bed rentals",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 637096
        },
        "quantity": 103,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-19T02:02:52.441Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-22T02:02:52.441Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hakeem",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Soft bed rentals, Jahangirabad, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 637096"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000296",
        "customerName": "Eric Carpenter",
        "phoneNumber": "9810615280",
        "email": "eric.carpenter@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#95",
            "addressLine1": "Luxury Lake",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 770396
        },
        "quantity": 622,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-18T00:40:17.123Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-21T00:40:17.123Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eric",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 83,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#95, Luxury Lake, Jahangirabad, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 770396"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000234",
        "customerName": "Dilan Anderson",
        "phoneNumber": "6159862639",
        "email": "dilan.anderson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "New House",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 669414
        },
        "quantity": 734,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-16T17:26:28.450Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-19T17:26:28.450Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dilan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, New House, Malviya Nagar, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 669414"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000356",
        "customerName": "Zaire Bell",
        "phoneNumber": "6066245285",
        "email": "zaire.bell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#76",
            "addressLine1": "Safe Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 629288
        },
        "quantity": 676,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-16T08:07:21.712Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-19T08:07:21.712Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zaire",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 87,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#76, Safe Homes, Bittan Market, Panaji, Goa. 629288"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000270",
        "customerName": "Elliot Quinn",
        "phoneNumber": "8463735146",
        "email": "elliot.quinn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#50",
            "addressLine1": "Sunny Place",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 750382
        },
        "quantity": 455,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-10T16:55:26.830Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-13T16:55:26.830Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Elliot",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#50, Sunny Place, Habib Ganj, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 750382"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000046",
        "customerName": "Yusuf Clark",
        "phoneNumber": "9139881584",
        "email": "yusuf.clark@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#37",
            "addressLine1": "One Uptown",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Dhuburi",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 132647
        },
        "quantity": 267,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-05T03:39:13.665Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-08T03:39:13.665Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Yusuf",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#37, One Uptown, Bairagarh, Dhuburi, Assam. 132647"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000262",
        "customerName": "Weston Reid",
        "phoneNumber": "6042496126",
        "email": "weston.reid@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 983591
        },
        "quantity": 222,
        "orderedDate": "2021-09-03T15:58:06.945Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-06T15:58:06.945Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Weston",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 67,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, Jolly City, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 983591"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000060",
        "customerName": "Timothy Mullins",
        "phoneNumber": "6257841932",
        "email": "timothy.mullins@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Life on the Green",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 548029
        },
        "quantity": 302,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-29T11:05:47.846Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-09-01T11:05:47.846Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Timothy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 93,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Life on the Green, MP Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 548029"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000284",
        "customerName": "Jordan Nava",
        "phoneNumber": "8549547211",
        "email": "jordan.nava@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "Blue Ribbon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 121239
        },
        "quantity": 371,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-24T19:18:22.819Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-27T19:18:22.819Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jordan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, Blue Ribbon Apartments, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 121239"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000446",
        "customerName": "Manuel Zimmerman",
        "phoneNumber": "8839962036",
        "email": "manuel.zimmerman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "Darling Building",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Vizianagaram",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 934860
        },
        "quantity": 570,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-23T22:13:09.875Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-26T22:13:09.875Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Manuel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, Darling Building, Habib Ganj, Vizianagaram, Andhra Pradesh. 934860"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000394",
        "customerName": "Kobe David",
        "phoneNumber": "8900771547",
        "email": "kobe.david@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#13",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Valsad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 509431
        },
        "quantity": 195,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-22T17:08:20.691Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-25T17:08:20.691Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kobe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#13, Homely Villas, Shivaji Nagar, Valsad, Gujarat. 509431"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000187",
        "customerName": "Lorelei Jarvis",
        "phoneNumber": "8146395471",
        "email": "lorelei.jarvis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "Wells Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Tirupati",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 517544
        },
        "quantity": 262,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-18T03:43:19.173Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-21T03:43:19.173Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lorelei",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, Wells Place Apartments, Jawahar Chowk, Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh. 517544"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000295",
        "customerName": "Lila Kelley",
        "phoneNumber": "8477247280",
        "email": "lila.kelley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "Harmony Park",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 222686
        },
        "quantity": 463,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-15T14:46:59.496Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-18T14:46:59.496Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lila",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, Harmony Park, Indrapuri, Delhi, Delhi. 222686"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000014",
        "customerName": "Jalen Boone",
        "phoneNumber": "7542857064",
        "email": "jalen.boone@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "The Twin Towers",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 386322
        },
        "quantity": 929,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-13T18:15:31.142Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-16T18:15:31.142Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jalen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, The Twin Towers, Malviya Nagar, New Delhi, Delhi. 386322"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000033",
        "customerName": "Luisa Jarvis",
        "phoneNumber": "9410292869",
        "email": "luisa.jarvis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Homes with peace",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 330647
        },
        "quantity": 962,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-11T07:04:25.197Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-14T07:04:25.197Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Luisa",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Homes with peace, Jawahar Chowk, New Delhi, Delhi. 330647"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000408",
        "customerName": "Danny Todd",
        "phoneNumber": "7767971825",
        "email": "danny.todd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#59",
            "addressLine1": "ApHEARTments",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Madhubani",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 334256
        },
        "quantity": 301,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-08T02:38:07.124Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-11T02:38:07.124Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Danny",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#59, ApHEARTments, Koh E Fiza, Madhubani, Bihar. 334256"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000128",
        "customerName": "Crew Gibbs",
        "phoneNumber": "7625501126",
        "email": "crew.gibbs@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "The Den",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 541597
        },
        "quantity": 470,
        "orderedDate": "2021-08-05T14:24:37.785Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-08-08T14:24:37.785Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Crew",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 90,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, The Den, Raisen Road, Madgaon, Goa. 541597"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000153",
        "customerName": "Haley Anderson",
        "phoneNumber": "8332640740",
        "email": "haley.anderson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "One Uptown",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 982387
        },
        "quantity": 518,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-23T03:19:50.794Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-26T03:19:50.794Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Haley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 36,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, One Uptown, Sultania Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 982387"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000074",
        "customerName": "Kyle Heath",
        "phoneNumber": "6965415883",
        "email": "kyle.heath@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#96",
            "addressLine1": "The Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Navsari",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 498390
        },
        "quantity": 224,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-21T18:50:19.241Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-24T18:50:19.241Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kyle",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#96, The Villas, Hoshangabad Road, Navsari, Gujarat. 498390"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000347",
        "customerName": "Rosalee Mullen",
        "phoneNumber": "9425759918",
        "email": "rosalee.mullen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Lilli Midtown Flats",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 160225
        },
        "quantity": 276,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-19T05:20:47.620Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-22T05:20:47.620Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rosalee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Lilli Midtown Flats, Peer Gate, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 160225"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000167",
        "customerName": "Xiomara Ali",
        "phoneNumber": "8951028568",
        "email": "xiomara.ali@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Life on the Green",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 742717
        },
        "quantity": 572,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-17T10:16:38.745Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-20T10:16:38.745Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Xiomara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 52,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Life on the Green, Kolar Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 742717"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000175",
        "customerName": "Rivka Aguirre",
        "phoneNumber": "6814869179",
        "email": "rivka.aguirre@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#24",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Canyon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 137411
        },
        "quantity": 904,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-17T05:11:06.504Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-20T05:11:06.504Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rivka",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 42,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#24, Hillside Canyon Apartments, Sultania Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 137411"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000257",
        "customerName": "Kinslee Greene",
        "phoneNumber": "9074139038",
        "email": "kinslee.greene@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "The Griffin",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Patan",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 584869
        },
        "quantity": 959,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-16T06:28:38.705Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-19T06:28:38.705Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kinslee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 49,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, The Griffin, Marvadi Road, Patan, Gujarat. 584869"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000130",
        "customerName": "Taylor Shepard",
        "phoneNumber": "7787001687",
        "email": "taylor.shepard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "The Fedora",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 334269
        },
        "quantity": 734,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-15T08:53:49.363Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-18T08:53:49.363Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Taylor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 69,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, The Fedora, Shivaji Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 334269"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000052",
        "customerName": "Wilson Simon",
        "phoneNumber": "9717999453",
        "email": "wilson.simon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Place",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 468910
        },
        "quantity": 758,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-14T13:02:42.567Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-17T13:02:42.567Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Wilson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 79,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, Sunshine Place, Hoshangabad Road, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 468910"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000113",
        "customerName": "Anya David",
        "phoneNumber": "6399851526",
        "email": "anya.david@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#92",
            "addressLine1": "House of Lords",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 972668
        },
        "quantity": 554,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-13T01:59:25.923Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-16T01:59:25.923Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Anya",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 40,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#92, House of Lords, Berasia Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 972668"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000444",
        "customerName": "Axl Dennis",
        "phoneNumber": "6940679613",
        "email": "axl.dennis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#41",
            "addressLine1": "MasterGlory",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 870664
        },
        "quantity": 646,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-12T12:43:35.352Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-15T12:43:35.352Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Axl",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#41, MasterGlory, Bittan Market, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 870664"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000155",
        "customerName": "Alondra Mora",
        "phoneNumber": "7630523394",
        "email": "alondra.mora@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#50",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 930784
        },
        "quantity": 738,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-09T16:56:23.462Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-12T16:56:23.462Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alondra",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#50, Jolly City, Arera Colony, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 930784"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000329",
        "customerName": "Maya Sloan",
        "phoneNumber": "7364082167",
        "email": "maya.sloan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Four Flamingo",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Khambhat",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 426364
        },
        "quantity": 549,
        "orderedDate": "2021-07-03T17:10:09.310Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-06T17:10:09.310Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Maya",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 56,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Four Flamingo, Sultania Road, Khambhat, Gujarat. 426364"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000231",
        "customerName": "Katelyn Gilmore",
        "phoneNumber": "8819396101",
        "email": "katelyn.gilmore@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Shoebox",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 721025
        },
        "quantity": 195,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-30T07:28:08.986Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-03T07:28:08.986Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Katelyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Shoebox, Jawahar Chowk, Madgaon, Goa. 721025"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000152",
        "customerName": "Garrett Bauer",
        "phoneNumber": "6979391664",
        "email": "garrett.bauer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 560257
        },
        "quantity": 307,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-29T20:04:18.242Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-02T20:04:18.242Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Garrett",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Jolly City, Shivaji Nagar, Madgaon, Goa. 560257"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000499",
        "customerName": "Teresa Lara",
        "phoneNumber": "7107973010",
        "email": "teresa.lara@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 620546
        },
        "quantity": 562,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-28T15:56:06.904Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-07-01T15:56:06.904Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Teresa",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 26,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, The Bend, Marvadi Road, Panaji, Goa. 620546"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000203",
        "customerName": "Thea Ellison",
        "phoneNumber": "9395344862",
        "email": "thea.ellison@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 385935
        },
        "quantity": 160,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-25T01:23:21.496Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-28T01:23:21.496Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Thea",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 44,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, Homely Villas, Govind Pura, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 385935"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000252",
        "customerName": "Benson Gibson",
        "phoneNumber": "7580609779",
        "email": "benson.gibson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "Newport Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Dehri",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 472438
        },
        "quantity": 358,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-18T04:58:27.047Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-21T04:58:27.047Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Benson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 24,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, Newport Apartments, Jahangirabad, Dehri, Bihar. 472438"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000162",
        "customerName": "Murphy Copeland",
        "phoneNumber": "7949353025",
        "email": "murphy.copeland@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#75",
            "addressLine1": "CappaCale Dale",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 990080
        },
        "quantity": 616,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-15T19:53:57.700Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-18T19:53:57.700Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Murphy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 50,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#75, CappaCale Dale, Hoshangabad Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 990080"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000439",
        "customerName": "Kaylee Landry",
        "phoneNumber": "7617909986",
        "email": "kaylee.landry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#83",
            "addressLine1": "Village Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 279734
        },
        "quantity": 540,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-14T11:26:45.937Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-17T11:26:45.937Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaylee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#83, Village Homes, Sultania Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 279734"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000263",
        "customerName": "Charlee Cohen",
        "phoneNumber": "7457909938",
        "email": "charlee.cohen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#48",
            "addressLine1": "The City Block",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Madhubani",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 196393
        },
        "quantity": 117,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-13T01:53:46.530Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-16T01:53:46.530Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Charlee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 10,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#48, The City Block, Sultania Road, Madhubani, Bihar. 196393"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000013",
        "customerName": "Veda Drake",
        "phoneNumber": "6346469384",
        "email": "veda.drake@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "EcoStay",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 188387
        },
        "quantity": 557,
        "orderedDate": "2021-06-04T08:13:22.980Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-06-07T08:13:22.980Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Veda",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, EcoStay, Kolar Road, Madgaon, Goa. 188387"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000163",
        "customerName": "Dayana Reeves",
        "phoneNumber": "6128347409",
        "email": "dayana.reeves@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#72",
            "addressLine1": "Sunny Place",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 276294
        },
        "quantity": 431,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-22T09:19:57.227Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-25T09:19:57.227Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dayana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#72, Sunny Place, Indrapuri, New Delhi, Delhi. 276294"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000255",
        "customerName": "Madilyn Pena",
        "phoneNumber": "8868981364",
        "email": "madilyn.pena@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Sun’s Rays Place",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 375364
        },
        "quantity": 134,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-11T21:39:02.839Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-14T21:39:02.839Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Madilyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Sun’s Rays Place, Kolar Road, Delhi, Delhi. 375364"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000072",
        "customerName": "Drake Olsen",
        "phoneNumber": "9355651191",
        "email": "drake.olsen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#82",
            "addressLine1": "Park Central Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 537317
        },
        "quantity": 863,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-11T12:23:56.583Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-14T12:23:56.583Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Drake",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#82, Park Central Apartments, Habib Ganj, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 537317"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000137",
        "customerName": "Cali Casey",
        "phoneNumber": "8370078945",
        "email": "cali.casey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Rockwell",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 446485
        },
        "quantity": 657,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-11T11:55:20.671Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-14T11:55:20.671Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cali",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 55,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Rockwell, Govind Pura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 446485"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000440",
        "customerName": "Jaxx Figueroa",
        "phoneNumber": "6774818981",
        "email": "jaxx.figueroa@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "Paradise Palms",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Gandhinagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 814681
        },
        "quantity": 454,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-10T11:30:34.986Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-13T11:30:34.986Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jaxx",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, Paradise Palms, TT Nagar, Gandhinagar, Gujarat. 814681"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000010",
        "customerName": "Ricky Sweeney",
        "phoneNumber": "9889369005",
        "email": "ricky.sweeney@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#86",
            "addressLine1": "Surf Rider Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 416342
        },
        "quantity": 591,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-10T04:28:57.373Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-13T04:28:57.373Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ricky",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 59,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#86, Surf Rider Apartments, Jahangirabad, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 416342"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000338",
        "customerName": "Harlan Gentry",
        "phoneNumber": "7799317675",
        "email": "harlan.gentry@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#55",
            "addressLine1": "Shoebox",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Anantapur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 383235
        },
        "quantity": 982,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-06T11:12:26.466Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-09T11:12:26.466Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Harlan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#55, Shoebox, Hoshangabad Road, Anantapur, Andhra Pradesh. 383235"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000032",
        "customerName": "Colin Branch",
        "phoneNumber": "7508879763",
        "email": "colin.branch@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#84",
            "addressLine1": "Park Place",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 398267
        },
        "quantity": 814,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-05T19:46:10.735Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-08T19:46:10.735Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Colin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#84, Park Place, Jahangirabad, Motihari, Bihar. 398267"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000434",
        "customerName": "Dario Conrad",
        "phoneNumber": "9128912611",
        "email": "dario.conrad@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#75",
            "addressLine1": "House of Lords",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 572286
        },
        "quantity": 918,
        "orderedDate": "2021-05-02T08:04:27.265Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-05T08:04:27.265Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dario",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#75, House of Lords, MP Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 572286"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000192",
        "customerName": "Crew McKay",
        "phoneNumber": "6252588401",
        "email": "crew.mckay@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#26",
            "addressLine1": "The Mill",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 440695
        },
        "quantity": 200,
        "orderedDate": "2021-04-30T21:05:03.148Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-05-03T21:05:03.148Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Crew",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 49,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#26, The Mill, MP Nagar, Dispur, Assam. 440695"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000084",
        "customerName": "Ayaan Lloyd",
        "phoneNumber": "9389504141",
        "email": "ayaan.lloyd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "Standard At Legacy",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 189358
        },
        "quantity": 208,
        "orderedDate": "2021-04-27T22:04:30.179Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-04-30T22:04:30.179Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ayaan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, Standard At Legacy, Raisen Road, Panaji, Goa. 189358"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000044",
        "customerName": "Kaiden Mann",
        "phoneNumber": "6740844933",
        "email": "kaiden.mann@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#90",
            "addressLine1": "Useful Units",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 704713
        },
        "quantity": 128,
        "orderedDate": "2021-04-26T14:43:51.427Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-04-29T14:43:51.427Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaiden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#90, Useful Units, TT Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 704713"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000214",
        "customerName": "Kason McDaniel",
        "phoneNumber": "9080567301",
        "email": "kason.mcdaniel@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "One Circular Quay",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Yemmiganur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 527294
        },
        "quantity": 108,
        "orderedDate": "2021-04-18T16:40:49.227Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-04-21T16:40:49.227Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kason",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 60,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, One Circular Quay, MP Nagar, Yemmiganur, Andhra Pradesh. 527294"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000116",
        "customerName": "Louie Blair",
        "phoneNumber": "6643553042",
        "email": "louie.blair@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#20",
            "addressLine1": "The Dorm Room",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 234228
        },
        "quantity": 230,
        "orderedDate": "2021-04-02T17:35:22.777Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-04-05T17:35:22.777Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Louie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#20, The Dorm Room, Habib Ganj, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 234228"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000246",
        "customerName": "Valentino Hampton",
        "phoneNumber": "8317654581",
        "email": "valentino.hampton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#68",
            "addressLine1": "Park Place",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 494164
        },
        "quantity": 243,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-30T01:13:27.577Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-04-02T01:13:27.577Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Valentino",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#68, Park Place, Bittan Market, Motihari, Bihar. 494164"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000171",
        "customerName": "Milan Waters",
        "phoneNumber": "7555495476",
        "email": "milan.waters@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "Ventura Ridge",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 648052
        },
        "quantity": 768,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-26T10:31:16.662Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-29T10:31:16.662Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Milan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, Ventura Ridge, Peer Gate, Panaji, Goa. 648052"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000304",
        "customerName": "Raphael Underwood",
        "phoneNumber": "7537879007",
        "email": "raphael.underwood@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Youth Motive",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Katihar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 481109
        },
        "quantity": 780,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-26T07:36:31.786Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-29T07:36:31.786Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Raphael",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Youth Motive, Raisen Road, Katihar, Bihar. 481109"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000337",
        "customerName": "Addison Grimes",
        "phoneNumber": "7158214529",
        "email": "addison.grimes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "MasterGlory",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Siwan",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 196961
        },
        "quantity": 216,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-25T14:34:28.240Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-28T14:34:28.240Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Addison",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, MasterGlory, Hamidia Road, Siwan, Bihar. 196961"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000471",
        "customerName": "Destiny Wagner",
        "phoneNumber": "9709450816",
        "email": "destiny.wagner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#24",
            "addressLine1": "The Griffin",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 593699
        },
        "quantity": 578,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-21T10:53:30.331Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-24T10:53:30.331Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Destiny",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#24, The Griffin, Indrapuri, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 593699"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000229",
        "customerName": "Ruth Rios",
        "phoneNumber": "6853361494",
        "email": "ruth.rios@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "The Niche Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Yemmiganur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 819506
        },
        "quantity": 876,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-11T13:06:56.110Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-14T13:06:56.110Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ruth",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 89,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, The Niche Apartments, Indrapuri, Yemmiganur, Andhra Pradesh. 819506"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000091",
        "customerName": "Renata Foley",
        "phoneNumber": "7460236812",
        "email": "renata.foley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#45",
            "addressLine1": "Ideal homes",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Raipur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 785981
        },
        "quantity": 784,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-10T14:18:23.922Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-13T14:18:23.922Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Renata",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 91,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#45, Ideal homes, Berasia Road, Raipur, Chhattisgarh. 785981"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000008",
        "customerName": "Thaddeus Rivers",
        "phoneNumber": "6975294162",
        "email": "thaddeus.rivers@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#50",
            "addressLine1": "Four Flamingo",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 662268
        },
        "quantity": 427,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-09T11:31:05.833Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-12T11:31:05.833Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Thaddeus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 11,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#50, Four Flamingo, Hoshangabad Road, Delhi, Delhi. 662268"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000038",
        "customerName": "Braxton Beltran",
        "phoneNumber": "8691183663",
        "email": "braxton.beltran@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Newport Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Dibrugarh",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 372572
        },
        "quantity": 559,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-05T14:36:01.677Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-08T14:36:01.677Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Braxton",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Newport Apartments, MP Nagar, Dibrugarh, Assam. 372572"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000318",
        "customerName": "Levi Oliver",
        "phoneNumber": "7552458792",
        "email": "levi.oliver@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#55",
            "addressLine1": "Spectrum on Spring",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Sivasagar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 567814
        },
        "quantity": 471,
        "orderedDate": "2021-03-02T07:56:31.431Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-03-05T07:56:31.431Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Levi",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#55, Spectrum on Spring, Jahangirabad, Sivasagar, Assam. 567814"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000070",
        "customerName": "Jakobe Morales",
        "phoneNumber": "7331722033",
        "email": "jakobe.morales@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#72",
            "addressLine1": "Blue Ribbon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Sitamarhi",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 889120
        },
        "quantity": 331,
        "orderedDate": "2021-02-25T21:31:15.807Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-28T21:31:15.807Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jakobe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#72, Blue Ribbon Apartments, Bittan Market, Sitamarhi, Bihar. 889120"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000308",
        "customerName": "Weston Larsen",
        "phoneNumber": "7182510513",
        "email": "weston.larsen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#54",
            "addressLine1": "RealBond Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 778425
        },
        "quantity": 738,
        "orderedDate": "2021-02-20T09:03:41.611Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-23T09:03:41.611Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Weston",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 33,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#54, RealBond Realty Rental, TT Nagar, Tinsukia, Assam. 778425"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000487",
        "customerName": "Frances Greer",
        "phoneNumber": "8274556940",
        "email": "frances.greer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 582408
        },
        "quantity": 216,
        "orderedDate": "2021-02-20T07:04:02.924Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-23T07:04:02.924Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Frances",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 40,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, La Grande Maison, Berasia Road, Guwahati, Assam. 582408"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000343",
        "customerName": "Marianna Rowe",
        "phoneNumber": "9624401893",
        "email": "marianna.rowe@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Skyline Condo",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 668104
        },
        "quantity": 502,
        "orderedDate": "2021-02-17T00:01:25.412Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-20T00:01:25.412Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marianna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Skyline Condo, Kolar Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 668104"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000047",
        "customerName": "Chloe Meyer",
        "phoneNumber": "8100336279",
        "email": "chloe.meyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Village Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 911363
        },
        "quantity": 179,
        "orderedDate": "2021-02-04T14:52:06.508Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-07T14:52:06.508Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Chloe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 68,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Village Villas, Berasia Road, Tezpur, Assam. 911363"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000174",
        "customerName": "Dash Chung",
        "phoneNumber": "8030356134",
        "email": "dash.chung@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#23",
            "addressLine1": "Creekside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Chapra",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 961355
        },
        "quantity": 152,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-31T08:22:51.462Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-02-03T08:22:51.462Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dash",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 32,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#23, Creekside Apartments, Shivaji Nagar, Chapra, Bihar. 961355"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000141",
        "customerName": "Guadalupe Zhang",
        "phoneNumber": "7651485130",
        "email": "guadalupe.zhang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "Timber Ridge Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 901417
        },
        "quantity": 484,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-25T13:59:28.175Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-28T13:59:28.175Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Guadalupe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 58,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, Timber Ridge Apartments, Indrapuri, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 901417"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000166",
        "customerName": "Landyn Larsen",
        "phoneNumber": "8682903797",
        "email": "landyn.larsen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#98",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 453155
        },
        "quantity": 652,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-24T17:38:26.078Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-27T17:38:26.078Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Landyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#98, La Grande Maison, Koh E Fiza, Madgaon, Goa. 453155"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000470",
        "customerName": "Titan Cohen",
        "phoneNumber": "9162951261",
        "email": "titan.cohen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Royal View",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Madhubani",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 535641
        },
        "quantity": 205,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-24T07:56:19.837Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-27T07:56:19.837Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Titan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 52,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Royal View, Hoshangabad Road, Madhubani, Bihar. 535641"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000411",
        "customerName": "Aria Fletcher",
        "phoneNumber": "9303687683",
        "email": "aria.fletcher@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "Youth Motive",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 284342
        },
        "quantity": 519,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-23T20:51:42.188Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-26T20:51:42.188Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aria",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, Youth Motive, Marvadi Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 284342"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000498",
        "customerName": "Coen Guevara",
        "phoneNumber": "8338568387",
        "email": "coen.guevara@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Blue Ribbon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Buxar",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 655311
        },
        "quantity": 801,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-23T04:34:50.106Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-26T04:34:50.106Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Coen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 37,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Blue Ribbon Apartments, Malviya Nagar, Buxar, Bihar. 655311"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000340",
        "customerName": "Kristian Hess",
        "phoneNumber": "6605281573",
        "email": "kristian.hess@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "Peace Waters",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 657485
        },
        "quantity": 709,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-22T15:21:22.699Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-25T15:21:22.699Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kristian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 30,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, Peace Waters, Jahangirabad, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 657485"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000290",
        "customerName": "Marcellus Rosales",
        "phoneNumber": "7427820836",
        "email": "marcellus.rosales@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 839223
        },
        "quantity": 596,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-21T05:50:22.674Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-24T05:50:22.674Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marcellus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Hillside Apartments, Bittan Market, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 839223"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000048",
        "customerName": "Tristan Acevedo",
        "phoneNumber": "6695998808",
        "email": "tristan.acevedo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#12",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Mahesana",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 782589
        },
        "quantity": 572,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-20T02:50:49.776Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-23T02:50:49.776Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tristan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 56,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#12, Jolly City, Bittan Market, Mahesana, Gujarat. 782589"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000474",
        "customerName": "Salvatore Hutchinson",
        "phoneNumber": "9809956899",
        "email": "salvatore.hutchinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "One Uptown",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 154017
        },
        "quantity": 833,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-17T05:47:20.364Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-20T05:47:20.364Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Salvatore",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, One Uptown, Koh E Fiza, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 154017"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000435",
        "customerName": "Bexley Valdez",
        "phoneNumber": "7995481843",
        "email": "bexley.valdez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "The Village View",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 508591
        },
        "quantity": 865,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-10T18:50:08.460Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-13T18:50:08.460Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Bexley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 36,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, The Village View, Peer Gate, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 508591"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000360",
        "customerName": "Reign Walsh",
        "phoneNumber": "7173247853",
        "email": "reign.walsh@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#66",
            "addressLine1": "Concrete homes",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 458357
        },
        "quantity": 976,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-01T12:11:25.608Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-04T12:11:25.608Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Reign",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#66, Concrete homes, Hoshangabad Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 458357"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000178",
        "customerName": "Jacob Rubio",
        "phoneNumber": "9711834289",
        "email": "jacob.rubio@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#77",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 107138
        },
        "quantity": 705,
        "orderedDate": "2021-01-01T09:32:26.178Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2021-01-04T09:32:26.178Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jacob",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#77, The Bend, Bairagarh, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 107138"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000180",
        "customerName": "Muhammad Torres",
        "phoneNumber": "9253695055",
        "email": "muhammad.torres@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Chandragiri",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 282317
        },
        "quantity": 134,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-25T05:10:26.583Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-28T05:10:26.583Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Muhammad",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, Homely Villas, Bittan Market, Chandragiri, Andhra Pradesh. 282317"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000353",
        "customerName": "Hana Herrera",
        "phoneNumber": "8498054714",
        "email": "hana.herrera@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "Park Place",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 358771
        },
        "quantity": 946,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-23T21:44:31.342Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-26T21:44:31.342Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Hana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, Park Place, Arera Colony, Delhi, Delhi. 358771"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000285",
        "customerName": "Scout Gardner",
        "phoneNumber": "7377705416",
        "email": "scout.gardner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#22",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 964667
        },
        "quantity": 584,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-22T13:23:15.218Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-25T13:23:15.218Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Scout",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#22, The Bend, Sultania Road, Panaji, Goa. 964667"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000225",
        "customerName": "Palmer Bonilla",
        "phoneNumber": "6959508659",
        "email": "palmer.bonilla@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#70",
            "addressLine1": "Village Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Dibrugarh",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 168285
        },
        "quantity": 832,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-18T13:01:59.021Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-21T13:01:59.021Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Palmer",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#70, Village Homes, Govind Pura, Dibrugarh, Assam. 168285"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000030",
        "customerName": "Pablo Magana",
        "phoneNumber": "7271982128",
        "email": "pablo.magana@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "Rockwell",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Vijayawada",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 481876
        },
        "quantity": 817,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-11T20:09:40.356Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-14T20:09:40.356Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Pablo",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, Rockwell, Hoshangabad Road, Vijayawada, Andhra Pradesh. 481876"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000119",
        "customerName": "Sariyah Turner",
        "phoneNumber": "7993444157",
        "email": "sariyah.turner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#79",
            "addressLine1": "Paradise Palms",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Yemmiganur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 713296
        },
        "quantity": 501,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-05T15:59:54.033Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-08T15:59:54.033Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sariyah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#79, Paradise Palms, Indrapuri, Yemmiganur, Andhra Pradesh. 713296"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000282",
        "customerName": "Jakob Roman",
        "phoneNumber": "9196524044",
        "email": "jakob.roman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Canyon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 480902
        },
        "quantity": 778,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-01T15:34:15.373Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-04T15:34:15.373Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jakob",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Hillside Canyon Apartments, Raisen Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 480902"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000352",
        "customerName": "Jovanni McCullough",
        "phoneNumber": "7563732250",
        "email": "jovanni.mccullough@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "Platinum Oaks",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 447428
        },
        "quantity": 429,
        "orderedDate": "2020-12-01T06:18:28.244Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-04T06:18:28.244Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jovanni",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 97,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, Platinum Oaks, TT Nagar, Panaji, Goa. 447428"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000232",
        "customerName": "Vihaan Klein",
        "phoneNumber": "8524720705",
        "email": "vihaan.klein@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Darling Building",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 179587
        },
        "quantity": 825,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-28T20:04:52.510Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-01T20:04:52.510Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Vihaan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Darling Building, Koh E Fiza, Delhi, Delhi. 179587"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000364",
        "customerName": "Benson York",
        "phoneNumber": "6880602983",
        "email": "benson.york@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "The Griffin",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Dhuburi",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 737734
        },
        "quantity": 249,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-28T05:52:55.905Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-12-01T05:52:55.905Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Benson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 61,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, The Griffin, Koh E Fiza, Dhuburi, Assam. 737734"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000012",
        "customerName": "Tomas Sheppard",
        "phoneNumber": "8585110211",
        "email": "tomas.sheppard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#87",
            "addressLine1": "Paradise Palms",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Kakinada",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 102145
        },
        "quantity": 702,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-09T19:45:07.963Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-11-12T19:45:07.963Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Tomas",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#87, Paradise Palms, Koh E Fiza, Kakinada, Andhra Pradesh. 102145"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000458",
        "customerName": "Emanuel Lucero",
        "phoneNumber": "7811273393",
        "email": "emanuel.lucero@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Rockwell",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 898369
        },
        "quantity": 531,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-07T09:58:42.002Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-11-10T09:58:42.002Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Emanuel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 47,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Rockwell, Raisen Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 898369"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000287",
        "customerName": "Chloe Lewis",
        "phoneNumber": "6358073452",
        "email": "chloe.lewis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#60",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 343164
        },
        "quantity": 483,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-06T20:03:07.864Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-11-09T20:03:07.864Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Chloe",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 46,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#60, Homely Villas, Arera Colony, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 343164"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000143",
        "customerName": "Logan Levy",
        "phoneNumber": "7853125285",
        "email": "logan.levy@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#63",
            "addressLine1": "Merril Willow Rental Co.",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 395592
        },
        "quantity": 232,
        "orderedDate": "2020-11-04T12:52:55.918Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-11-07T12:52:55.918Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Logan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 86,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#63, Merril Willow Rental Co., Jawahar Chowk, Madgaon, Goa. 395592"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000068",
        "customerName": "Malakai Mercado",
        "phoneNumber": "9839155848",
        "email": "malakai.mercado@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Hillside Canyon Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 146742
        },
        "quantity": 695,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-31T11:44:43.828Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-11-03T11:44:43.828Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Malakai",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 18,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Hillside Canyon Apartments, Bairagarh, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 146742"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000393",
        "customerName": "Elle Ortega",
        "phoneNumber": "9630224961",
        "email": "elle.ortega@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "Park Central Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Kadapa",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 962618
        },
        "quantity": 616,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-28T08:17:47.728Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-10-31T08:17:47.728Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Elle",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 48,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, Park Central Apartments, Shahpura, Kadapa, Andhra Pradesh. 962618"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000486",
        "customerName": "Dariel Blair",
        "phoneNumber": "7908672308",
        "email": "dariel.blair@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#58",
            "addressLine1": "Homes for all",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 706450
        },
        "quantity": 692,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-25T06:28:29.449Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-10-28T06:28:29.449Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dariel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 93,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#58, Homes for all, Bairagarh, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 706450"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000079",
        "customerName": "Aitana Hendrix",
        "phoneNumber": "6966155315",
        "email": "aitana.hendrix@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#84",
            "addressLine1": "Joyful Place",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Nagaon",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 945232
        },
        "quantity": 869,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-25T03:26:58.529Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-10-28T03:26:58.529Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aitana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#84, Joyful Place, Kolar Road, Nagaon, Assam. 945232"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000086",
        "customerName": "Colby Robinson",
        "phoneNumber": "8292018569",
        "email": "colby.robinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Ahmadabad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 732575
        },
        "quantity": 118,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-19T11:37:21.925Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-10-22T11:37:21.925Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Colby",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 47,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, The Bend, Shivaji Nagar, Ahmadabad, Gujarat. 732575"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000059",
        "customerName": "Izabella Ryan",
        "phoneNumber": "7911452481",
        "email": "izabella.ryan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Machilipatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 751486
        },
        "quantity": 679,
        "orderedDate": "2020-10-09T12:44:02.527Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-10-12T12:44:02.527Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Izabella",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 70,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, La Grande Maison, Marvadi Road, Machilipatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 751486"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000027",
        "customerName": "Parker Padilla",
        "phoneNumber": "6015890736",
        "email": "parker.padilla@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "Ample Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 136393
        },
        "quantity": 997,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-27T20:04:19.514Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-30T20:04:19.514Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Parker",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 92,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, Ample Apartments, Govind Pura, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 136393"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000083",
        "customerName": "Samantha Huang",
        "phoneNumber": "6392147073",
        "email": "samantha.huang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "Joyous Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 903031
        },
        "quantity": 483,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-26T12:29:16.824Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-29T12:29:16.824Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Samantha",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 59,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, Joyous Homes, Peer Gate, Delhi, Delhi. 903031"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000249",
        "customerName": "Kaylee Villa",
        "phoneNumber": "8249464415",
        "email": "kaylee.villa@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#29",
            "addressLine1": "Safe Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 228640
        },
        "quantity": 795,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-24T05:36:08.110Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-27T05:36:08.110Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kaylee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#29, Safe Homes, Hamidia Road, Delhi, Delhi. 228640"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000092",
        "customerName": "Mohammad Robinson",
        "phoneNumber": "9331890702",
        "email": "mohammad.robinson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "One Eighties Residences",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Sivasagar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 727478
        },
        "quantity": 115,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-21T23:58:51.264Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-24T23:58:51.264Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mohammad",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, One Eighties Residences, Bittan Market, Sivasagar, Assam. 727478"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000004",
        "customerName": "Thaddeus Zhang",
        "phoneNumber": "6115422473",
        "email": "thaddeus.zhang@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#63",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 586580
        },
        "quantity": 775,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-21T00:02:01.040Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-24T00:02:01.040Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Thaddeus",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#63, Town Place Apartments, Bittan Market, New Delhi, Delhi. 586580"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000276",
        "customerName": "Callum May",
        "phoneNumber": "9221626764",
        "email": "callum.may@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#35",
            "addressLine1": "Silver House",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 822907
        },
        "quantity": 304,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-19T17:40:24.574Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-22T17:40:24.574Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Callum",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#35, Silver House, Koh E Fiza, Dispur, Assam. 822907"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000309",
        "customerName": "Xiomara Conley",
        "phoneNumber": "9078821074",
        "email": "xiomara.conley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "Harvest Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Tezpur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 727232
        },
        "quantity": 106,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-17T00:08:20.152Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-20T00:08:20.152Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Xiomara",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, Harvest Lofts, Arera Colony, Tezpur, Assam. 727232"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000031",
        "customerName": "Amaris Rojas",
        "phoneNumber": "8191419093",
        "email": "amaris.rojas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Platinum Oaks",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 145629
        },
        "quantity": 493,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-14T08:56:05.833Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-17T08:56:05.833Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Amaris",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 12,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Platinum Oaks, Indrapuri, Madgaon, Goa. 145629"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000438",
        "customerName": "Matthew Patterson",
        "phoneNumber": "8706283128",
        "email": "matthew.patterson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Surf Rider Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Saharsa",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 394721
        },
        "quantity": 530,
        "orderedDate": "2020-09-05T12:45:08.081Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-08T12:45:08.081Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Matthew",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 14,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Surf Rider Apartments, Shivaji Nagar, Saharsa, Bihar. 394721"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000432",
        "customerName": "Ernesto Kramer",
        "phoneNumber": "8190221723",
        "email": "ernesto.kramer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#73",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Palanpur",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 104866
        },
        "quantity": 297,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-29T07:50:20.969Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-09-01T07:50:20.969Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ernesto",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#73, Town Place Apartments, Malviya Nagar, Palanpur, Gujarat. 104866"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000280",
        "customerName": "Kade Lynch",
        "phoneNumber": "9045704816",
        "email": "kade.lynch@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "The River",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 607101
        },
        "quantity": 945,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-27T04:59:02.655Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-30T04:59:02.655Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kade",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, The River, MP Nagar, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 607101"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000120",
        "customerName": "Joshua Solomon",
        "phoneNumber": "6053082658",
        "email": "joshua.solomon@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "EcoStay",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 863690
        },
        "quantity": 792,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-26T23:33:06.147Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-29T23:33:06.147Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Joshua",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, EcoStay, Jahangirabad, Guwahati, Assam. 863690"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000416",
        "customerName": "Braden Huff",
        "phoneNumber": "7403241681",
        "email": "braden.huff@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#34",
            "addressLine1": "Harvest Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 207267
        },
        "quantity": 640,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-23T10:39:19.757Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-26T10:39:19.757Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Braden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 54,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#34, Harvest Lofts, Shivaji Nagar, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 207267"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000186",
        "customerName": "William Patton",
        "phoneNumber": "6885537637",
        "email": "william.patton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#36",
            "addressLine1": "Joyful Place",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Guwahati",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 382278
        },
        "quantity": 551,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-16T01:37:02.127Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-19T01:37:02.127Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "William",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#36, Joyful Place, Jahangirabad, Guwahati, Assam. 382278"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000168",
        "customerName": "Arjun Becker",
        "phoneNumber": "6511610252",
        "email": "arjun.becker@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#64",
            "addressLine1": "Eastern Suburbs",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Gandhinagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 272512
        },
        "quantity": 142,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-13T12:43:57.471Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-16T12:43:57.471Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Arjun",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 10,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#64, Eastern Suburbs, Malviya Nagar, Gandhinagar, Gujarat. 272512"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000073",
        "customerName": "Oaklyn Joseph",
        "phoneNumber": "7409538777",
        "email": "oaklyn.joseph@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#92",
            "addressLine1": "Homely Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Nagarjunakoṇḍa",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 331050
        },
        "quantity": 864,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-13T11:45:08.622Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-16T11:45:08.622Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Oaklyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#92, Homely Villas, Hamidia Road, Nagarjunakoṇḍa, Andhra Pradesh. 331050"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000307",
        "customerName": "Karsyn Russell",
        "phoneNumber": "8205539685",
        "email": "karsyn.russell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "Exotic homes",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Gandhinagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 583705
        },
        "quantity": 816,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-12T11:25:17.021Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-15T11:25:17.021Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Karsyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 53,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, Exotic homes, Sultania Road, Gandhinagar, Gujarat. 583705"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000335",
        "customerName": "Chaya Kaur",
        "phoneNumber": "9350072459",
        "email": "chaya.kaur@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "The Twin Towers",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Patan",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 422092
        },
        "quantity": 219,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-12T06:06:07.496Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-15T06:06:07.496Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Chaya",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, The Twin Towers, Govind Pura, Patan, Gujarat. 422092"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000292",
        "customerName": "Phoenix Ramsey",
        "phoneNumber": "9468726431",
        "email": "phoenix.ramsey@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#46",
            "addressLine1": "WinterSpring Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 996434
        },
        "quantity": 735,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-11T06:28:31.199Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-14T06:28:31.199Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Phoenix",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 82,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#46, WinterSpring Rental, Habib Ganj, Motihari, Bihar. 996434"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000361",
        "customerName": "Leia Anthony",
        "phoneNumber": "8649171230",
        "email": "leia.anthony@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#32",
            "addressLine1": "East Side Living",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Kadapa",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 561119
        },
        "quantity": 877,
        "orderedDate": "2020-08-10T03:00:59.747Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-13T03:00:59.747Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leia",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 14,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#32, East Side Living, Indrapuri, Kadapa, Andhra Pradesh. 561119"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000313",
        "customerName": "Ivy Bruce",
        "phoneNumber": "9452176750",
        "email": "ivy.bruce@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#98",
            "addressLine1": "Grand at the Dominion",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 571403
        },
        "quantity": 605,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-30T12:14:33.122Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-08-02T12:14:33.122Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ivy",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#98, Grand at the Dominion, Govind Pura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 571403"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000345",
        "customerName": "Dani Bravo",
        "phoneNumber": "8998070778",
        "email": "dani.bravo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "The Palm Springs",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 484866
        },
        "quantity": 718,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-28T13:02:07.743Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-31T13:02:07.743Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, The Palm Springs, Marvadi Road, Panaji, Goa. 484866"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000291",
        "customerName": "Kinley Estrada",
        "phoneNumber": "9247303186",
        "email": "kinley.estrada@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#18",
            "addressLine1": "Cove Property",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Chapra",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 153214
        },
        "quantity": 167,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-25T05:04:12.329Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-28T05:04:12.329Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kinley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 27,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#18, Cove Property, Govind Pura, Chapra, Bihar. 153214"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000449",
        "customerName": "Emery Patrick",
        "phoneNumber": "9294537855",
        "email": "emery.patrick@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#81",
            "addressLine1": "The Den",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 814235
        },
        "quantity": 290,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-19T19:24:45.882Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-22T19:24:45.882Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Emery",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#81, The Den, Indrapuri, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 814235"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000241",
        "customerName": "Aurora Jordan",
        "phoneNumber": "7462837955",
        "email": "aurora.jordan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#21",
            "addressLine1": "Ample Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 299238
        },
        "quantity": 970,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-19T13:34:46.384Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-22T13:34:46.384Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aurora",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 47,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#21, Ample Apartments, Sultania Road, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 299238"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000275",
        "customerName": "Zariah Frazier",
        "phoneNumber": "7238196409",
        "email": "zariah.frazier@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#67",
            "addressLine1": "Eastern Suburbs",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Yemmiganur",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 584727
        },
        "quantity": 465,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-15T01:37:55.191Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-18T01:37:55.191Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zariah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 95,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#67, Eastern Suburbs, Jawahar Chowk, Yemmiganur, Andhra Pradesh. 584727"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000357",
        "customerName": "Melody Duncan",
        "phoneNumber": "7906467138",
        "email": "melody.duncan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "Merril Willow Rental Co.",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Bhagalpur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 690033
        },
        "quantity": 610,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-13T01:16:01.581Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-16T01:16:01.581Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Melody",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 16,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, Merril Willow Rental Co., Govind Pura, Bhagalpur, Bihar. 690033"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000483",
        "customerName": "Dream Larsen",
        "phoneNumber": "8821197576",
        "email": "dream.larsen@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#10",
            "addressLine1": "CappaCale Dale",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 740532
        },
        "quantity": 792,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-09T10:18:16.239Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-12T10:18:16.239Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dream",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 58,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#10, CappaCale Dale, Sultania Road, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 740532"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000426",
        "customerName": "Zechariah Reilly",
        "phoneNumber": "8144319990",
        "email": "zechariah.reilly@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#49",
            "addressLine1": "GreenHexa Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 942031
        },
        "quantity": 970,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-07T03:40:35.014Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-10T03:40:35.014Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zechariah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 65,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#49, GreenHexa Realty Rental, Hoshangabad Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 942031"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000144",
        "customerName": "Harold Ponce",
        "phoneNumber": "7093194911",
        "email": "harold.ponce@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "Passion homes",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Jagdalpur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 857444
        },
        "quantity": 734,
        "orderedDate": "2020-07-02T11:36:42.230Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-07-05T11:36:42.230Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Harold",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 69,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, Passion homes, Koh E Fiza, Jagdalpur, Chhattisgarh. 857444"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000382",
        "customerName": "Krew Levy",
        "phoneNumber": "6225603162",
        "email": "krew.levy@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#44",
            "addressLine1": "Eastern Suburbs",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 690965
        },
        "quantity": 265,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-24T16:35:20.444Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-27T16:35:20.444Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Krew",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#44, Eastern Suburbs, Hoshangabad Road, Tinsukia, Assam. 690965"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000005",
        "customerName": "Sarai Bennett",
        "phoneNumber": "9601874885",
        "email": "sarai.bennett@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#23",
            "addressLine1": "MiniPalais",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 472895
        },
        "quantity": 675,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-23T07:05:36.960Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-26T07:05:36.960Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sarai",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#23, MiniPalais, Govind Pura, Madgaon, Goa. 472895"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000245",
        "customerName": "Dulce Pittman",
        "phoneNumber": "6749767164",
        "email": "dulce.pittman@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#23",
            "addressLine1": "Platinum Oaks",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Visakhapatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 174062
        },
        "quantity": 486,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-18T02:40:49.884Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-21T02:40:49.884Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Dulce",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 94,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#23, Platinum Oaks, Berasia Road, Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 174062"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000274",
        "customerName": "Josue Todd",
        "phoneNumber": "6293519667",
        "email": "josue.todd@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "Life on the Green",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 494367
        },
        "quantity": 241,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-17T00:54:52.618Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-20T00:54:52.618Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Josue",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 39,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, Life on the Green, Jahangirabad, Panaji, Goa. 494367"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000102",
        "customerName": "Cayden Sheppard",
        "phoneNumber": "6243760813",
        "email": "cayden.sheppard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#53",
            "addressLine1": "The Station",
            "addressLine2": "Malviya Nagar",
            "city": "Dispur",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 488336
        },
        "quantity": 168,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-09T21:43:37.894Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-12T21:43:37.894Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Cayden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 75,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#53, The Station, Malviya Nagar, Dispur, Assam. 488336"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000159",
        "customerName": "Milena Hensley",
        "phoneNumber": "8586667717",
        "email": "milena.hensley@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#31",
            "addressLine1": "Sunshine Place",
            "addressLine2": "Govind Pura",
            "city": "Dehri",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 481044
        },
        "quantity": 199,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-07T18:34:34.968Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-10T18:34:34.968Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Milena",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 55,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#31, Sunshine Place, Govind Pura, Dehri, Bihar. 481044"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000424",
        "customerName": "Sage Conner",
        "phoneNumber": "6200949051",
        "email": "sage.conner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#12",
            "addressLine1": "Stanley Park Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Samastipur",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 596580
        },
        "quantity": 482,
        "orderedDate": "2020-06-04T00:31:28.961Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-07T00:31:28.961Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Sage",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 34,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#12, Stanley Park Apartments, Habib Ganj, Samastipur, Bihar. 596580"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000040",
        "customerName": "Wilson Benton",
        "phoneNumber": "7645595480",
        "email": "wilson.benton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#61",
            "addressLine1": "East Side Living",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 919017
        },
        "quantity": 676,
        "orderedDate": "2020-05-29T03:04:58.345Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-06-01T03:04:58.345Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Wilson",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#61, East Side Living, Raisen Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 919017"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000075",
        "customerName": "Amani Flowers",
        "phoneNumber": "6484109106",
        "email": "amani.flowers@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "Town Place Walkups",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Motihari",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 423528
        },
        "quantity": 502,
        "orderedDate": "2020-05-12T01:23:14.080Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-05-15T01:23:14.080Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Amani",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 28,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, Town Place Walkups, Indrapuri, Motihari, Bihar. 423528"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000380",
        "customerName": "Marvin Powers",
        "phoneNumber": "9023947507",
        "email": "marvin.powers@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#30",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 874634
        },
        "quantity": 571,
        "orderedDate": "2020-05-10T04:18:25.255Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-05-13T04:18:25.255Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Marvin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#30, La Grande Maison, Habib Ganj, Silchar, Assam. 874634"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000219",
        "customerName": "Kyleigh Blackburn",
        "phoneNumber": "9163232727",
        "email": "kyleigh.blackburn@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "MiniPalais",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Kurnool",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 505029
        },
        "quantity": 542,
        "orderedDate": "2020-05-04T10:37:25.529Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-05-07T10:37:25.529Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Kyleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 25,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, MiniPalais, Sultania Road, Kurnool, Andhra Pradesh. 505029"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000118",
        "customerName": "Rowan Frederick",
        "phoneNumber": "8855510745",
        "email": "rowan.frederick@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#71",
            "addressLine1": "Village Homes",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "Junagadh",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 575027
        },
        "quantity": 995,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-27T09:06:20.669Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-30T09:06:20.669Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rowan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#71, Village Homes, Hoshangabad Road, Junagadh, Gujarat. 575027"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000110",
        "customerName": "Alden Jordan",
        "phoneNumber": "7745630189",
        "email": "alden.jordan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#14",
            "addressLine1": "Apartment Partners",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 615791
        },
        "quantity": 417,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-25T23:24:02.985Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-28T23:24:02.985Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alden",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 96,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#14, Apartment Partners, TT Nagar, Madgaon, Goa. 615791"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000029",
        "customerName": "Esperanza Page",
        "phoneNumber": "6886872762",
        "email": "esperanza.page@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#33",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Hamidia Road",
            "city": "Ahmadabad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 966223
        },
        "quantity": 269,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-25T13:17:00.426Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-28T13:17:00.426Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Esperanza",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#33, La Grande Maison, Hamidia Road, Ahmadabad, Gujarat. 966223"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000261",
        "customerName": "Anne Russell",
        "phoneNumber": "9867003996",
        "email": "anne.russell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#50",
            "addressLine1": "Village Villas",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 991208
        },
        "quantity": 597,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-25T13:06:16.085Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-28T13:06:16.085Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Anne",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 49,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#50, Village Villas, Shahpura, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 991208"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000123",
        "customerName": "Rylie Hines",
        "phoneNumber": "6460376885",
        "email": "rylie.hines@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#55",
            "addressLine1": "MasterGlory",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Bilaspur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 328877
        },
        "quantity": 558,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-14T18:37:08.852Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-17T18:37:08.852Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rylie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#55, MasterGlory, Kolar Road, Bilaspur, Chhattisgarh. 328877"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000490",
        "customerName": "Jax Khan",
        "phoneNumber": "6347926323",
        "email": "jax.khan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#21",
            "addressLine1": "Silver House",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Durg",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 246770
        },
        "quantity": 275,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-07T09:19:28.437Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-10T09:19:28.437Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jax",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 77,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#21, Silver House, Habib Ganj, Durg, Chhattisgarh. 246770"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000112",
        "customerName": "Blake Barron",
        "phoneNumber": "9519161873",
        "email": "blake.barron@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "MiniPalais",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 145454
        },
        "quantity": 722,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-07T00:28:32.882Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-10T00:28:32.882Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Blake",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 23,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, MiniPalais, Bairagarh, Delhi, Delhi. 145454"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000390",
        "customerName": "Denver English",
        "phoneNumber": "7120590595",
        "email": "denver.english@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#82",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Patna",
            "state": "Bihar",
            "pincode": 255084
        },
        "quantity": 609,
        "orderedDate": "2020-04-06T18:30:41.970Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-09T18:30:41.970Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Denver",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 62,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#82, City Dwellers, MP Nagar, Patna, Bihar. 255084"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000199",
        "customerName": "Paulina Henson",
        "phoneNumber": "7352447495",
        "email": "paulina.henson@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#57",
            "addressLine1": "One Eighties Residences",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Jamnagar",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 981795
        },
        "quantity": 757,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-29T17:44:21.883Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-04-01T17:44:21.883Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paulina",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 51,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#57, One Eighties Residences, Arera Colony, Jamnagar, Gujarat. 981795"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000368",
        "customerName": "Davian Douglas",
        "phoneNumber": "7469374433",
        "email": "davian.douglas@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "Village Villas",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Raipur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 113475
        },
        "quantity": 865,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-24T14:25:52.251Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-27T14:25:52.251Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Davian",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 33,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, Village Villas, MP Nagar, Raipur, Chhattisgarh. 113475"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000103",
        "customerName": "Veda Phan",
        "phoneNumber": "6955671562",
        "email": "veda.phan@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#28",
            "addressLine1": "Stanley Park Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 483484
        },
        "quantity": 407,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-20T23:01:53.915Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-23T23:01:53.915Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Veda",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 80,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#28, Stanley Park Apartments, Marvadi Road, Delhi, Delhi. 483484"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000037",
        "customerName": "Ayla Tran",
        "phoneNumber": "8160472048",
        "email": "ayla.tran@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "Passion homes",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 779079
        },
        "quantity": 797,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-15T04:45:16.866Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-18T04:45:16.866Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ayla",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, Passion homes, Marvadi Road, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 779079"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000165",
        "customerName": "Eliza Singleton",
        "phoneNumber": "6697019419",
        "email": "eliza.singleton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "Homes for all",
            "addressLine2": "Jawahar Chowk",
            "city": "Itanagar",
            "state": "Arunachal Pradesh",
            "pincode": 955687
        },
        "quantity": 213,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-14T13:36:39.535Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-17T13:36:39.535Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eliza",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 15,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, Homes for all, Jawahar Chowk, Itanagar, Arunachal Pradesh. 955687"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000461",
        "customerName": "Everleigh Davenport",
        "phoneNumber": "7650281259",
        "email": "everleigh.davenport@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#36",
            "addressLine1": "Homes with peace",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Ambikapur",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 969943
        },
        "quantity": 885,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-10T19:52:29.157Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-13T19:52:29.157Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Everleigh",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 21,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#36, Homes with peace, Sultania Road, Ambikapur, Chhattisgarh. 969943"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000067",
        "customerName": "Londyn Marquez",
        "phoneNumber": "7919728526",
        "email": "londyn.marquez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "Creekside Apartments",
            "addressLine2": "Arera Colony",
            "city": "Tinsukia",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 155631
        },
        "quantity": 257,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-07T02:07:29.971Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-10T02:07:29.971Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Londyn",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, Creekside Apartments, Arera Colony, Tinsukia, Assam. 155631"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000305",
        "customerName": "Ensley Kent",
        "phoneNumber": "7586822790",
        "email": "ensley.kent@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#69",
            "addressLine1": "Ideal homes",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Srikakulam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 856616
        },
        "quantity": 515,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-06T06:44:01.431Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-09T06:44:01.431Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Ensley",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "White",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 22,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#69, Ideal homes, Shahpura, Srikakulam, Andhra Pradesh. 856616"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000087",
        "customerName": "Nora Farmer",
        "phoneNumber": "7880975640",
        "email": "nora.farmer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#22",
            "addressLine1": "ApHEARTments",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 703364
        },
        "quantity": 285,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-04T08:36:33.417Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-07T08:36:33.417Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Nora",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 66,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#22, ApHEARTments, Sultania Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 703364"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000303",
        "customerName": "Viviana Cobb",
        "phoneNumber": "9798234850",
        "email": "viviana.cobb@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "Jolly City",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 334209
        },
        "quantity": 836,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-04T00:22:15.019Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-07T00:22:15.019Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Viviana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 71,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, Jolly City, Peer Gate, Madgaon, Goa. 334209"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000497",
        "customerName": "Rhea Avalos",
        "phoneNumber": "7379906142",
        "email": "rhea.avalos@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#91",
            "addressLine1": "City Dwellers",
            "addressLine2": "Kolar Road",
            "city": "Silchar",
            "state": "Assam",
            "pincode": 535343
        },
        "quantity": 675,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-03T17:53:57.080Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-06T17:53:57.080Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rhea",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 84,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#91, City Dwellers, Kolar Road, Silchar, Assam. 535343"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000494",
        "customerName": "Alec Vo",
        "phoneNumber": "8172736206",
        "email": "alec.vo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#11",
            "addressLine1": "The River",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Bharuch",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 102280
        },
        "quantity": 651,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-03T07:49:14.253Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-06T07:49:14.253Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Alec",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 88,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#11, The River, Jahangirabad, Bharuch, Gujarat. 102280"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000351",
        "customerName": "Rachel O’Connell",
        "phoneNumber": "8345671769",
        "email": "rachel.o’connell@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Rockwell",
            "addressLine2": "Sultania Road",
            "city": "Machilipatnam",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 160379
        },
        "quantity": 819,
        "orderedDate": "2020-03-01T09:20:07.764Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-03-04T09:20:07.764Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Rachel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 29,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Rockwell, Sultania Road, Machilipatnam, Andhra Pradesh. 160379"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000151",
        "customerName": "Lilyana Horton",
        "phoneNumber": "7297357198",
        "email": "lilyana.horton@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#56",
            "addressLine1": "Useful Units",
            "addressLine2": "Shahpura",
            "city": "Rajahmundry",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 825706
        },
        "quantity": 280,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-25T18:55:45.274Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-28T18:55:45.274Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lilyana",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "L",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 93,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#56, Useful Units, Shahpura, Rajahmundry, Andhra Pradesh. 825706"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000442",
        "customerName": "Anakin Cortes",
        "phoneNumber": "8991141643",
        "email": "anakin.cortes@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#52",
            "addressLine1": "The Twin Towers",
            "addressLine2": "Bairagarh",
            "city": "Junagadh",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 406360
        },
        "quantity": 892,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-24T12:11:27.689Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-27T12:11:27.689Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Anakin",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 47,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#52, The Twin Towers, Bairagarh, Junagadh, Gujarat. 406360"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000202",
        "customerName": "Jack Brewer",
        "phoneNumber": "8664413478",
        "email": "jack.brewer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#78",
            "addressLine1": "Harvest Lofts",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 158527
        },
        "quantity": 309,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-23T22:41:09.108Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-26T22:41:09.108Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Jack",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#78, Harvest Lofts, Bittan Market, Madgaon, Goa. 158527"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000081",
        "customerName": "Aila McDaniel",
        "phoneNumber": "9575557286",
        "email": "aila.mcdaniel@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#72",
            "addressLine1": "Harmony Park",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 502321
        },
        "quantity": 291,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-22T18:28:48.683Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-25T18:28:48.683Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Aila",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#72, Harmony Park, Marvadi Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 502321"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000350",
        "customerName": "Lucas Pena",
        "phoneNumber": "9276815050",
        "email": "lucas.pena@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#93",
            "addressLine1": "La Grande Maison",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 998974
        },
        "quantity": 309,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-21T00:53:11.942Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-24T00:53:11.942Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Lucas",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 74,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#93, La Grande Maison, Shivaji Nagar, Panaji, Goa. 998974"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000125",
        "customerName": "Zoey Gould",
        "phoneNumber": "8880858029",
        "email": "zoey.gould@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#80",
            "addressLine1": "Darling Building",
            "addressLine2": "Marvadi Road",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 160944
        },
        "quantity": 615,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-18T07:01:36.687Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-21T07:01:36.687Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zoey",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 17,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#56298",
            "price": 872
        },
        "completeAddress": "#80, Darling Building, Marvadi Road, Kheda, Gujarat. 160944"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000148",
        "customerName": "Brayan Sawyer",
        "phoneNumber": "6284819470",
        "email": "brayan.sawyer@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#38",
            "addressLine1": "Sun’s Rays Place",
            "addressLine2": "MP Nagar",
            "city": "Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 164092
        },
        "quantity": 386,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-10T21:54:44.026Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-13T21:54:44.026Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Brayan",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XL",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 98,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#38, Sun’s Rays Place, MP Nagar, Delhi, Delhi. 164092"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000164",
        "customerName": "Clark Romero",
        "phoneNumber": "9022601823",
        "email": "clark.romero@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#51",
            "addressLine1": "The Jacks",
            "addressLine2": "Jahangirabad",
            "city": "Rajnandgaon",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 898455
        },
        "quantity": 233,
        "orderedDate": "2020-02-04T21:55:14.622Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-07T21:55:14.622Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Clark",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 68,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#51, The Jacks, Jahangirabad, Rajnandgaon, Chhattisgarh. 898455"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000465",
        "customerName": "Paislee Valdez",
        "phoneNumber": "9797623715",
        "email": "paislee.valdez@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#27",
            "addressLine1": "Passion homes",
            "addressLine2": "Berasia Road",
            "city": "Bhuj",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 608882
        },
        "quantity": 164,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-30T17:10:13.534Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-02-02T17:10:13.534Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Paislee",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 99,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#27, Passion homes, Berasia Road, Bhuj, Gujarat. 608882"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000094",
        "customerName": "Zion Huynh",
        "phoneNumber": "7240981591",
        "email": "zion.huynh@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#63",
            "addressLine1": "RealBond Realty Rental",
            "addressLine2": "Habib Ganj",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 271268
        },
        "quantity": 220,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-26T17:33:43.723Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-29T17:33:43.723Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Zion",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 20,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#63, RealBond Realty Rental, Habib Ganj, Madgaon, Goa. 271268"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000193",
        "customerName": "Leanna Tanner",
        "phoneNumber": "6853848523",
        "email": "leanna.tanner@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#82",
            "addressLine1": "The Bend",
            "addressLine2": "Peer Gate",
            "city": "Dowlaiswaram",
            "state": "Andhra Pradesh",
            "pincode": 279542
        },
        "quantity": 718,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-22T15:23:17.489Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-25T15:23:17.489Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Leanna",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 48,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#82, The Bend, Peer Gate, Dowlaiswaram, Andhra Pradesh. 279542"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000448",
        "customerName": "Forest Ruiz",
        "phoneNumber": "9879327735",
        "email": "forest.ruiz@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#65",
            "addressLine1": "New House",
            "addressLine2": "Hoshangabad Road",
            "city": "New Delhi",
            "state": "Delhi",
            "pincode": 473805
        },
        "quantity": 534,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-16T00:22:49.150Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-19T00:22:49.150Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Forest",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "M",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 72,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#65, New House, Hoshangabad Road, New Delhi, Delhi. 473805"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000260",
        "customerName": "Carlos Mathis",
        "phoneNumber": "7260665219",
        "email": "carlos.mathis@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#47",
            "addressLine1": "One Uptown",
            "addressLine2": "Raisen Road",
            "city": "Kheda",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 900690
        },
        "quantity": 683,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-15T20:12:25.092Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-18T20:12:25.092Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Carlos",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Navy Blue",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 41,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92834",
            "price": 823
        },
        "completeAddress": "#47, One Uptown, Raisen Road, Kheda, Gujarat. 900690"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000378",
        "customerName": "Connor Galindo",
        "phoneNumber": "8079072128",
        "email": "connor.galindo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#15",
            "addressLine1": "The Jacks",
            "addressLine2": "Bittan Market",
            "city": "Madgaon",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 645789
        },
        "quantity": 288,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-13T08:04:29.161Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-16T08:04:29.161Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Connor",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 64,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#15, The Jacks, Bittan Market, Madgaon, Goa. 645789"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000339",
        "customerName": "Amelie McIntosh",
        "phoneNumber": "6611895097",
        "email": "amelie.mcintosh@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#25",
            "addressLine1": "Darling Building",
            "addressLine2": "Indrapuri",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 796291
        },
        "quantity": 997,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-12T19:27:31.707Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-15T19:27:31.707Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Amelie",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XXL",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 57,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#09823",
            "price": 687
        },
        "completeAddress": "#25, Darling Building, Indrapuri, Panaji, Goa. 796291"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000306",
        "customerName": "Mekhi Huff",
        "phoneNumber": "8314320676",
        "email": "mekhi.huff@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#89",
            "addressLine1": "One Eighties Residences",
            "addressLine2": "Shivaji Nagar",
            "city": "Morbi",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 474871
        },
        "quantity": 968,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-10T14:08:33.188Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-13T14:08:33.188Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Mekhi",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 73,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#92837",
            "price": 635
        },
        "completeAddress": "#89, One Eighties Residences, Shivaji Nagar, Morbi, Gujarat. 474871"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000022",
        "customerName": "Eliel Galindo",
        "phoneNumber": "6376277625",
        "email": "eliel.galindo@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#42",
            "addressLine1": "Skyline Condo",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Valsad",
            "state": "Gujarat",
            "pincode": 426953
        },
        "quantity": 856,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-08T00:43:24.008Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-11T00:43:24.008Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Eliel",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Black",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 13,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#93458",
            "price": 734
        },
        "completeAddress": "#42, Skyline Condo, TT Nagar, Valsad, Gujarat. 426953"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000484",
        "customerName": "Brycen Maynard",
        "phoneNumber": "8737953479",
        "email": "brycen.maynard@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#94",
            "addressLine1": "Sunny Place",
            "addressLine2": "TT Nagar",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 560097
        },
        "quantity": 198,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-07T19:39:07.710Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-10T19:39:07.710Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Brycen",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "S",
            "color": "Olive Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 81,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#94, Sunny Place, TT Nagar, Panaji, Goa. 560097"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000254",
        "customerName": "Harold Bates",
        "phoneNumber": "6106173248",
        "email": "harold.bates@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#36",
            "addressLine1": "East Side Living",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Panaji",
            "state": "Goa",
            "pincode": 939471
        },
        "quantity": 463,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-07T06:01:29.123Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-10T06:01:29.123Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Harold",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Green",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 63,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#87324",
            "price": 2384
        },
        "completeAddress": "#36, East Side Living, Koh E Fiza, Panaji, Goa. 939471"
    },
    {
        "orderNumber": "ORD#000342",
        "customerName": "Azariah Corona",
        "phoneNumber": "6988221913",
        "email": "azariah.corona@mail.com",
        "address": {
            "houseNo": "#88",
            "addressLine1": "The Den",
            "addressLine2": "Koh E Fiza",
            "city": "Dhamtari",
            "state": "Chhattisgarh",
            "pincode": 435971
        },
        "quantity": 471,
        "orderedDate": "2020-01-01T04:31:56.881Z",
        "deliveryDate": "2020-01-04T04:31:56.881Z",
        "specificDetails": {
            "nameOnTShirt": "Azariah",
            "sizeOfTShirt": "XS",
            "color": "Brown",
            "printInfoFront": "INDIA",
            "printInfoBack": 68,
            "logoOrDesign": false,
            "catalogueNumber": "SHIRT#16523",
            "price": 1832
        },
        "completeAddress": "#88, The Den, Koh E Fiza, Dhamtari, Chhattisgarh. 435971"
    }
]